Every relationship's a power struggle.
Some of us need to be controlled.
Why did you first start listening to me?
I just followed your lead.
- I don't want to be a leader.
- I want my position moved
to the risk management department.
If we pull milestone cases
like Washington Township...
There's not much we can do here today.
Closing the plant is not an option.
I'm being pressured to resign.
Not doing anything to help.
What did you say your name was?
- I'm Ollie.
- This is a rubber ducky.
It'll pull all cached passwords.
It can get every email,
text message, and document.
You guys just got hacked.
Jesus, what is that noise?
Tape's busted. Grab another one.
All of you can't accept the fact
that maybe we fucked up.
Who knows who's gonna be
waiting for you at home?
Dark Army, FBI, cops.
He hacked me and stole
my dog on top of it.
That proves it was him.
Where do you think you are right now?
- What do you mean?
- You haven't been staying
with your mother.
People always told me growing up
that it's never about the destination.
It's about the journey.
But what if the destination
is you?
Elliot Alderson.
Are you Elliot Alderson?
Mr. Alderson, you're under arrest
for unauthorized use of a computer,
computer trespass, and grand larceny.
- Grab the computers.
- Let's go.
Get the hard drives.
All the USB drives.
- Any digital media.
- Yes, sir.
Check everywhere.
Get animal control here for the dog.
Let's go. Let's go.
Put your arms up. Spread 'em.
Put your left thumb on there.
- You suicidal?
- No.
- You a drug addict?
- You on any medication?
- No.
- How you feeling right now?
- Great.
I've spoken with the prosecutor,
and we can get the
hacking charges reduced.
The theft charge is a
little more difficult.
The plaintiff is really
upset about the dog,
but I think we can negotiate.
Hey, you heard what I said, right?
When the judge asks you for a plea
you say,
"Not guilty."
Got it?
In the case of People vs. Alderson
how does the defendant plead?
Guilty.
You're shitting me.
Mr. Alderson,
you do realize Mr. Lenny Shannon's dog
was an expensive purchase at $1,200?
That makes your theft a felony.
Let the record show,
Mr. Alderson nodded his head
up and down indicating "yes,"
and you're admitting you hacked into Mr.
Shannon's email,
social media, and bank accounts,
which will convict you on both counts
of computer hacking?
Again, let the record show,
Mr. Alderson nodded his head
up and down indicating "yes."
You're aware of the gravity
of these allegations?
You will be sentenced to jail.
What the fuck are you doing?
Yes...
and I plead guilty.
Do you make this plea out of free will
- and free mind?
- No! No.
He's fucking crazy.
Yes.
Mr. Alderson, I declare you guilty
of computer hacking, computer trespass,
grand larceny of fourth degree.
I hereby sentence you to
18 months in county jail.
Adios, you son of a bitch.
- This your first time here?
- Yes.
Do you have any intention
of harming yourself?
- No.
- Sit.
Don't move.
Put your chin on the bull's-eye.
Do not move.
Right side.
All right, let's go.
Need you to swing by at 3:00 p.m.
Problems with RT again.
Yes sir, Warden.
Let's go.
Get naked.
Let's go. Get undressed.
Hurry up. All right, let's go.
Get undressed for me.
Squat down. Turn around.
Let me see the bottoms of your feet.
Your left foot. Now bend over.
Spread your ass. Bend over.
Spread 'em.
Read this right here,
confirm that these are
all of your items,
and sign right here.
Speedy Gonzalez.
Fucking amazing, man.
Arrested, arraigned,
convicted within 24 hours.
Yeah, we heard about you, cuz.
In fact,
you're the only guilty
man in the entire pen.
You know that?
Leon.
Okay, that's cool.
It's best you learn soon,
'cause you don't wanna be
alone in a place like this.
Check it out. I'll give you the lowdown.
Routine. That's key.
It's best you find your routine,
whatever it is, and stick to it.
Mornings, we chow.
Afternoons, we hit the ball court.
Evenings, that's when I get my TV time.
Some people join church
groups, or AA, or whatever,
but I like to bench personally.
Peace, brother.
Ain't no Internet for us here.
Your best bet is going
through some boxes
in the library full of old,
throwback classic DVDs.
You know what I'm saying?
I'm making my way through
the '90s right now.
Nearly finished with "Mad About You."
You know, my man Paul Reiser...
he just doesn't get the
credit he deserve.
Man is spectacular.
Phenomenal.
Think I'ma start watching
"Seinfeld" next.
I heard it's nails.
You look nervous, cuz.
Don't be.
Just do you.
I mean, I'd say we got a pretty solid
rapport going on anyway.
We stick together,
things'll be just fine.
Oh, that's Hot Carla.
If you're a pyro,
she's your chick with a dick.
Know what I'm saying?
Probably not.
Oh, whatever you do
stay away from these David Duke
motherfuckers right here, man.
You don't say much, do you?
- No.
- Well, that's cool, man.
I'm here to provide you
with anything you may need.
I can pretty much find
anything, and I mean anything.
Smokes, pills, hard shit,
porn, grandma porn.
Some of these guys like that shit.
Gay porn.
I don't judge, man.
Whatever you need.
Can you get me a notebook?
See you in the morning.
That's how it happened.
That's all you missed.
That's everything.
- sync and corrections by Caio -
- www.addic7ed.com -
You got everything you arrived with?
Sign here stating such.
Here's a discharge report
and the early release form.
Give that to the officers at the door.
You have the hack to
thank for that letter.
I never released this many
non-violent offenders before.
This mess with the economy
is affecting the prison budgets too.
You got lucky. Don't squander it.
That card's worthless out there now.
You want it for sentimental value,
or should I toss it?
Toss it.
Init 5, return to normal.
Is it possible to return
after 86 days in a 6x9-foot box?
Init 5 is supposed to
bring color and sound.
Instead the world's gray and quiet.
Joseph Green's office. Monica speaking.
Hi, Monica. I'm a junior partner
at Johnson, Lerner, and Carlin.
I have sensitive documents for Mr.
Green regarding
- this Flint water case.
- Send them over.
I'll make sure he gets them right away.
I'm actually downstairs right now.
Super. Leave 'em at reception.
I'm sorry. I was told these are
very sensitive documents
and to only deliver them
straight to Mr. Green
or your hands.
Sorry. I can't leave my desk,
but Mr. Green is out of
the office until 2:00,
so he's not gonna read
them right away anyway.
Obviously I would just
bring them up myself,
but security down here is insane.
Can you please just come down?
Okay, I'll be right down.
Oh, hey.
Monica.
Uh, tell Joe to give me a call
when he gets back from lunch, will you?
Sure.
Hurry up.
I hacked my Dark Army contact.
Found an archive with screenshots
of his IRC chats with them.
Something called Stage 2.
It has to do with the femtocell.
I tried to tell Trenton and Mobley,
but I couldn't get in touch
with either of them.
I called, message checked
all the usual haunts.
Both are AWOL.
Okay, Trenton's parents are a wreck.
They filed a missing person's report.
Between them missing and
the channel archive
I'm freaking out.
I think Dark Army could
be cleaning house.
That doesn't make sense.
I think they're behind my early release.
We need to talk to your contact.
We're not
really on the best of terms right now.
Doesn't matter.
They can't do this.
This wasn't part of the deal.
Let's keep moving.
Out through the basement,
I'll leave through
the side door, and we'll
meet at the seven.
Not yet.
I'm going to see her.
What do you mean?
I thought this was
just to lose our tail.
Elliot, you're actually
gonna go see her?
We seriously need to talk.
Shit has gone down.
I need to do this.
Okay.
Just be quick.
I'll wait in the stairwell.
Mom?
They taking care of you?
Room looks nice.
I'll see if they can fix the clock.
Looks like it's broken.
How are you?
A lot's happened
since last I saw you.
Had a really hard time.
Anyway,
just wanted to say thank you.
You helped me survive
these last couple months.
I don't think I could
have done it without you.
Okay.
Take care.
_
Init 5 is supposed to be simple.
A fresh start.
Restored connections.
This may be my first
real moment of normalcy.
Taking a piss in private.
You hit me in the face
with a fucking bat!
Thank God I didn't need stitches!
Well, I should have hit you harder.
We've been over this for
the last three weeks.
Okay, I've walked you through
every IRC conversation.
I am not gonna let this go.
Why the fuck are you
sending pictures of me
while I'm asleep to the Dark Army?
How many times do I have to tell you?
Letting them know that you're
with me keeps you safe.
I was trying to protect you.
Then why aren't you
telling me about Stage 2
and what you guys did
with the femtocell?
We've been over this a million...
You've both got to calm down!
Yes, the shit has
officially hit the fan.
Here's what we're gonna do.
Okay, okay. Let's all take a beat.
We're gonna settle down here.
Relax.
Elliot?
Hey, Elliot. You all right?
Come back to Earth.
I thought you wanted to
find Mobley and Trenton?
Yeah.
We need to know what
happened to them, right?
I can't keep up with you two.
Look, I'm not risking my
life to help with this.
I'm not doing it. I'm not doing it.
Your Dark Army contact.
You have one?
You must.
If they find out I was
involved, it'll be my ass.
Okay? I'll be the next one missing.
Only there won't be any questions
about where I went.
You better be more
reliable than your sister.
Hey,
what the hell just happened?
I was gonna ask you the same.
Why were you talking with them?
What are you talking about?
One second everything was normal.
All of a sudden, you stopped responding.
It was like you shut down.
I had to say something.
It's unfortunate what both your country
and the company have been through
in the last several weeks.
Yes.
A succession of unfortunate events.
The timing of which
almost seems intentional.
Well, at least there's
good news for both of us.
Your little pet project
came through even better
than you thought.
I must admit, she surprised me.
It's a good thing that she did
the right thing in the end.
It's too bad.
You know, for all she's done,
it won't matter.
The failure of the
bailout has left me in
a rather obsequious position.
We failed our financial stress test,
so we won't be able
to keep up all our facilities.
As of noon this Friday,
I'm sorry to say, the
Washington Township plant
will be taken over
by the federal government.
And here I thought we were
taking a step forward,
but here we stand two steps back.
Your actions remind me of
your predecessor, Phillip.
And here comes the veiled death threat.
You wanna take a shot at me?
Be my guest.
The appointment of a new CEO
isn't going to stop the
federal government
from taking over the plant.
I flew for 13 hours and 35 minutes,
if you have a point, it's time.
I needed that bailout money,
and I no longer have it.
Thanks to your little shootout in China.
What do I need now?
Cash.
Lots of it.
I could see a scenario where
the Chinese government,
in a bid to establish itself
as the new global leader
of the 21st century,
loans E Corp the money it needs...
At a low interest rate.
Perhaps even zero.
As a gesture of goodwill
to the American people.
With that cash, I could save your plant
from the clutches of the
federal government,
and finally,
when a peaceful China
appears benevolent,
well...
That's an easier pitch
for me to get onto the President's desk.
I will be happy to go back and talk
with the Chinese government.
I'm sure that they will
be most agreeable,
but the next time you
threaten my plant...
What?
The only move left in that
scenario is a third World War.
You see? I'm a mercenary.
I don't play fair.
I play what I want.
When you deal with a mercenary,
then all decorum gets
tossed out the window,
so you go ahead with your cute threats
and your watch beeps.
Order
will not protect you anymore, my friend.
I will rain chaos,
even if it hurts me,
'cause I would rather see you lose
than win myself.
Oh.
That's all the time I have.
On May 9th, we took down
the world's biggest conglomerate.
We all had the same intention...
me, Darlene, Mobley, Trenton, Romero...
to change the world,
but there was one other player,
the Dark Army.
We never did find out what
their intentions were.
Pwnie Express pwn phone.
A phone loaded with 103 network
monitoring and attack tools.
A dream device for
pentesters and hackers.
His name is Xun.
Xun's boss is Whiterose,
who helped us bring down Evil Corp.
Xun and his people wanted the femtocell.
Why?
I don't know,
but soon we'll know everything.
We're hacking Xun.
Something's not right.
I feel off.
It's like we're overheating.
We'll be fine.
We're up. I've got a connection.
Time to set the meet with Xun.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, wait.
No, no, no.
I thought we were operating from here?
This only gets his phone mic live.
I'm going to ask them about Stage 2.
What?
Even if they don't tell me anything,
at least it'll get
them talking about it,
and that's all we need right now.
Oh, my God. Jesus, bro,
you're just like your sister.
First the number. Now the meet.
I mean, you don't stop.
I'm not doing it, man.
These guys won't think twice
about killing you on the spot.
Trust me.
I have a way to get him talking.
Fuck yeah. I would love to meet him.
No, he's not meeting you.
He's meeting Mr. Robot.
What'd you say?
Nothing.
I meant me.
Me. He's meeting me.
Something's happening with us.
We can't do this.
I got this.
This is big.
How did you get...
The levels of toxicity are still
above regulation,
right?
What's the next course of
action in a case like this?
Uh, well, this definitely
falls under what we call
substantial and specific danger
to public health and safety.
You know we're bound by law
to protect your anonymity, right?
There could be money
for a whistle-blower
in a situation like this.
You're gonna wanna get a lawyer.
I'm not doing this for the money.
I just want it to happen fast.
Okay.
I'll take this to the deputy director.
You mind sticking around for a while?
No.
Hey!
Hey...
All right, yo. This is our stop.
Yo, I don't get it.
Are you nervous or something, man?
- Because you can't be...
- No, I...
Never mind. I'm good.
_
Flying drone into the capital
of this great nation.
Meanwhile, the FBI
gets caught with its
hand in the cookie jar
trying to work in legal gray areas.
Listening in on phone calls.
Reading emails.
The FBI has 3 million of
you innocent citizens
under surveillance for no reason.
Okay? The backlash?
It boggles the mind.
If you've got nothing to hide
then what do you have to worry about?
Especially, at a little surveillance?
- Oh, shit.
- Help bring down
the world's worst criminals.
The FBI needs to catch this guy
by what... means necessary.
...symbol of capitalism.
Unless it falls on the
capital's doorstep
that's not vandalism.
That's a victory lap, people!
Tyrell Wellick wants us to know,
he's not done...
_
- Why are they leaving?
- They weren't expecting you.
Look at me!
Tell Whiterose I wanna
know what Stage 2 is.
Second one tonight.
Brownouts. We've been bracing ourselves
since Comet Electric went on strike.
I'm sorry to keep you waiting.
Deputy Director Phelps.
Office of Investigations.
- Hi.
- Jeff told me a little about
what you've brought us.
Can you come with me?
My colleagues and I wanted
to ask you a few questions.
We're so indebted to citizens like you.
Thank you.
I never cease to be
astonished by the heroics
of everyday people.
Did you come all the way down
from New York just for this?
Or are you based in New Jersey?
You know, I should probably get
some contact information from you.
- Jeff promised anonymity.
- Which is a nice idea,
to be sure.
Is Jeff going to be in the meeting?
I know. It sounds complicated,
but how it works is the
commission will want
to discuss this with
you after they review.
Maybe I'm misunderstanding, but...
You do work at E Corp, yes?
What?
I never said that.
What is your position there?
The more we know about the
origins of these documents
the quicker we can process them.
Actually, could I get my
files and the drive back?
You've made it all the way down here.
Let's not stop now, shall we?
I'm sorry.
This trip has taken a lot
longer than I thought it would,
and I can't miss the last train back.
But, Angela, my colleagues
in the other room are
eager to talk to you.
No, thanks.
I gotta go.
- How'd it go?
- Everything's on track.
Good.
The lights have been flickering.
Yeah. The streetlights too.
- Brownout's started.
- Hey.
I gotta talk to you for a minute.
I left that busted VHS
tape at the Smart House.
- What VHS tape?
- That fsociety video.
Relax. I'm sure we got it.
- We cleaned the place good.
- No, I left it.
It's not here.
We wiped the whole house down.
Do you remember grabbing it?
I know I didn't.
- We have to go back.
- Oh, Jesus Christ, Darlene.
We cannot go back. That
was a goddamn month ago.
The cops could have been there already,
and you're just remembering this now?
It doesn't matter. I have to go.
Fucking hell, Darlene. I swear.
Why are you even using VHS
tapes in the first place?
Because it's cool?
There's a million filters on Final Cut.
My face is on that tape.
Fine. Fine,
but I'm going, all right?
Feds are looking for you, not me.
Where is it?
I think I set it on that weird lamp
in the living room.
Maybe it fell behind.
All right.
Uh, hang on.
Thank you.
Really.
You look burnt.
Yeah, I'm getting tired.
You can stay here and
crash on the couch.
Home would be better.
I'm not feeling right.
They're gonna be watching.
All the more reason.
I need them to see me
living a normal life.
Oh, good point,
but assume the worst.
Your place is probably bugged.
Be careful coming back here.
I'll stay up and keep listening.
Hey, one of your fellow tenants
let me in the building.
Look what I got.
Your favorite. Nia's gyros.
Mind if I come in?
Actually, yeah. I'm...
Don't worry. I left
my handcuffs at home.
Wow.
Gosh.
Nice place.
They really take good
care of you here, huh?
E Corp housing?
Are you working for them?
Working for who, Angela?
I need you to leave.
I had this dream,
which if you know me, is pretty rare.
It was good at first.
Exciting.
There was the beautiful woman.
Sexy even.
But then, man, did it go downhill fast.
By the end, I was being
choked underwater.
Ollie Parker told me
about the CD at Allsafe.
It was literally the first
thing out of his mouth
when we interviewed him two months ago.
I've been having you tracked ever since.
Including your little field trip
out there to the Nuclear
Regulatory Commission today.
It's clear you're freaking
out about something.
I don't know how any
of this ties together,
but...
eventually someone
will connect the dots,
and it'll catch up to you.
So I'm being real with you right now.
Next person's not gonna offer you food.
They're gonna grab you off the street
and throw you in a dark cell.
But you still have one hand to play.
That's me.
In that dream I had,
when I was being drowned,
it was when I stopped fighting it.
When I finally let go
and stopped struggling so much...
That's when I survived.
_
- _
- Elliot.
_
It began as a failure.
Everything.
My existence.
I should recognize that.
Accept it.
For me there's no such
thing as normalcy.
My dead father appears
and disappears at will.
I talk to you, an invisible friend.
I'd ask if you're normal,
but you never talk back.
_
How can I return to normal
when the SUV belonging
to the man I murdered
is parked outside my apartment?
Normal?
I have no normal.
Hello, Ollie.
- sync and corrections by Caio -
- www.addic7ed.com -