It's almost as if
something's come alive.
My perfectly constructed loop.
At 8:00 a.m. breakfast
with my friend Leon.
At 2:00 p.m. we'll check
out a basketball game.
Two days a week I go to a church group.
You could use some practice.
If he's guilty,
I could destroy him at a terminal.
I told you not to look.
- Hi, Daddy.
- Hi, pumpkin.
You were drunk, eating shrimp cocktail,
and it was raining
when you decided my mother would die?
If you want to change things,
perhaps you should try from within.
You want me to convince the class
to remove the contingency.
You're gonna give me exactly
what I want in return.
I can't wipe the security footage
of you planting the femtocell.
Angela Moss.
You won't be able to give me
anything I want out of life.
Oh, I think so.
Oh, oh, Tyrell, Joanna,
meet my silent partner in crime,
Sharon Knowles.
I've heard many good things.
- And her husband, Scott.
- How are things?
Tyrell here is our new rising young star
with an eye on the CTO position.
But he's gonna have to wait
for Terry Colby's golf
career to take off
or for an early stroke.
Those earrings are stunning.
Thank you.
Tyrell's always surprising
me with little gifts.
Capitalistic pig!
- Synca and correctins by Caio -
- www.addic7ed.com -
Hello.
I see you.
I recognize you.
I acknowledge your existence.
Let's talk.
Get to know who each other really are.
All of this is said with
a simple act of a handshake
between two people.
It's not any different than a client
connecting with a server.
It all relies on that first handshake
and naturally grows from there
for most people.
For me,
I can't seem to learn the rules.
What happened back there?
When you protected me.
What was that? I've
never seen that before.
That was what you needed.
Why were you trying to hide him?
- What are you talking about?
- Tyrell.
You were acting like he
wasn't in the trunk.
But Tyrell was there.
I saw him.
I thought we moved past this.
Let's not go backwards.
What are you so afraid will happen
if you tell me the truth?
Why do you want to know so bad?
Why do you even fucking care?
I don't want to be in denial anymore.
I just want to accept what I did...
and move on.
Fine.
I'll tell you.
What's the last thing that you remember?
Pop... popcorn.
I-I remember the popcorn.
Who the fuck?
I'm sorry, would you mind
holding for a moment?
Thanks.
I'll make this quick.
I'm Agent DiPierro, FBI
Cybercrime Division.
We co-opted one of your floors.
I was heading to my station when
I see you.
And it wasn't an "oops, wrong
floor" kind of drop-in.
From where I was, it looked like
you were coming from somewhere.
Now, this is nothing official
so don't worry, but...
I just had to ask,
what were you doing on
a restricted floor?
Making plans
with Agent Thomas.
We were trying to decide
drinks tomorrow or
lunch today.
Where'd you land?
Lunch.
A Greek place nearby.
How do you know each other?
I'm sorry, is there something else
I can help you with?
I just
really have to get back to
this call before lunch.
You know, this is the honest,
"cards on the table" truth,
your story fascinates me.
The luck...
To leave Allsafe a week before
the company gets hacked
and then to end up here at E Corp.
It's ironic given your history.
Okay, don't freak. She's got nothing.
If she did, you'd already be busted.
Well, I should quit babbling.
I was gonna have you
drop by soon anyway.
Drop by?
For what?
Just to get a statement, answer
a few questions, no big.
I'd be happy to.
I'm just really busy right now.
Whatever this is...
It's not you.
Okay, final command,
ifconfig,
space,
wlan1, space, up.
And there it is.
What?
We just owned the FBI.
I did it, didn't I?
It was either us
or him.
How did I do it?
Elliot...
the guy was fucking batshit.
He was raving about
killing some woman and...
the wonder of it all.
I mean, we were gonna be next.
How did I do it?
After I ran the scripts,
he went off on us being gods.
The popcorn,
that's where Darlene
said she hid that gun.
And I didn't want to, but...
I shot him.
No.
Harder.
I told my friends you're coming.
You know that can't happen.
I thought this was our celebration.
We love each other. What's to hide?
Derek.
I mean, how many times
do you get to turn 30?
Either come to my party
tonight as my girlfriend
or we're done.
Pull up two hours ago.
Last week, any day.
The entire archive's corrupt.
Call the network team.
You guys just got hacked.
I'd sweep the 23rd floor and
check Angela Moss's computer.
You won't find anything... I'm
sure she erased all traces...
but check anyway.
Where you going?
It's Fourth of July tomorrow.
I'm gonna find a barbeque
to be miserable at.
Trash pile-ups have now become
a real epidemic in the city.
Due to the credit crisis
brought on by Five/Nine,
many private businesses cannot afford
waste management services,
which has sparked a cottage industry of
roadside garbage burning
at discounted rates.
The Taxi and Limousine
Commission asks that
drivers now accept Ecoin.
Per the Taxi and Limousine Commission,
payment can be made via mobile phone.
Just download the Ecoin
app from the Play Store
or App Store, scan the QR code
once you reach your destination,
and the payment will be withdrawn
from your Ecoin Wallet.
You had me worried, not
answering my calls
after all that went down.
I'm gonna go.
You weren't the target.
Cisco was just trying...
Stop.
I know you already put
the rest together, so...
no more smokescreens.
Okay, ask me anything, I'm an open book.
I owe you that.
You guys always thought that
you were smarter than me.
But come on.
You never actually hid it that well.
Every Halloween,
when we were kids,
you and Elliot always made me
watch that shitty scary movie.
It was so bad.
And all these years later,
I'd kind of forgotten about it.
Even when the masks started
popping up in those videos.
I didn't place it at first.
Maybe I did.
Maybe I didn't want to.
I mean, come on,
that's crazy, right?
That you guys would...
Had enough alone time down there
to get your head right and
do what needs to be done?
Speak up.
Yeah.
You believe him?
Okay.
This is how it's gonna go.
You gonna sit your ass right here
until you do what you got to do.
Once the site's up,
you gonna crawl back into your hole
until we're sure this baby's
purring like a kitten.
How long is this gonna take?
A few hours.
Once he gets what he wants...
Right now he needs me.
So that makes us safe.
What's with the looks?
Mm.
And this is happening tomorrow?
Mm-hmm.
Hello, Derek.
You never showed up.
Told you what would happen
if you didn't show up.
No-no-no-no-no, that's
not gonna work anymore.
You've been messing with
me for way too long.
I should've known
somebody that I met working
at a stuck-up E Corp party
would be bad news.
Meeting you at that party
changed something for me.
I'd be lost right now without you.
What you want,
I want it too.
I was busy tonight because I was
hassling my lawyer on holiday
to do this.
It's my birthday gift to you.
Holy shit.
We're getting more traffic than ever.
Says our Bitcoin intake
doubled since we've been up.
200,000 we could have
made while we were down,
that's on you, boy.
It's time to go back to
your cage, shitbrick.
What about a game?
Old time's sake.
Give me and Elliot a minute.
Wait outside.
All right, set it up.
Thank you.
For what?
When we first met, I
thought I was helping you.
I thought I was gonna be your savior.
I didn't tell you about my wife.
She was so smart.
Way smarter than me.
She was like you,
real good with computers.
That's what she did for a living.
So when she had this idea to do a site,
it sounded good to me.
I don't think she ever meant
it to go where it went.
She was wanting to make
some extra scratch.
But the thing grew so fast,
it took on a life of its own.
And the money,
well...
We're talking about the
type of money that
makes you question right and wrong.
So, you know,
we made a deal.
Decided we'd let the market dictate
what was sold on the site.
And we wouldn't look.
She was better at the denial than me.
It ate at me,
all the things I imagined were going on.
I feared the worst.
But I still didn't look.
Not until you came along.
After I found out what was on there,
what we did to you,
what we did to RT,
it was weak.
Way back when,
when I said it was about stumbling,
I was wrong.
I should've taken a fucking stand.
You are my answer.
It's not the other way around.
So thank you.
How much time do I have?
Come on, man.
We both knew exactly
what you were gonna do
when I let you go back on that computer.
With their response time,
I would guess they have
us surrounded by now.
You better get out before
they get up here then.
World champion chess
master Emanuel Lasker
once said,
"When you see a good move...
look for a better one."
Elliot.
Be careful.
I gave Ray the chance
to make the right move.
And he left himself wide open to me.
When I completed the migration,
I also took it upon
myself to open the site
to more than just TOR traffic.
Stay right here and don't move.
Just had to index it on
a few search engines
and with the added touch of adverts
on the top advertising sites,
and now it's accessible
to any average scumbag
that Googles "Thai girls for sale."
Didn't take long for the FBI to catch on
after I emailed them an anonymous tip.
Mr. Robot was a part of me that
I created because of my pain.
So now we have a chance to start again.
Our handshake negotiated us as partners.
The House will come to order.
There has been much mystery
surrounding the vandalism and castration
of the Wall Street bull.
That mystery was solved when
the missing anatomy of the bull
crashed through a skylight
of the House chamber.
Police, FBI, and the Department
of Homeland Security
have begun a full-fledged manhunt
for those parties responsible.
You haven't answered my
calls since the weekend.
As you can see, it's busy.
Ever since this bailout
fiasco yesterday,
these kits are flying off the shelves.
The, uh, end of civilization is near,
so this is gonna have to wait.
I can settle the lawsuit.
Stay out of that.
The lawyers are handling it.
E Corp will settle.
But there's a contingency with
the independent inspections.
If we drop it...
I'm not discussing this with you.
If you drop the independent inspections,
they will settle.
Did... did your boss put you up to this?
Look at what's happening.
Who knows if this company
will be around long enough
to see this case through?
Drop the contingency.
You'll get your money.
The inspections are there for a reason.
Do you want what happened to your mom
to happen again?
I'll make sure the inspections
go forward internally.
Is that how they're suckering you?
Trust me, they value me over there.
You laugh,
but they respect me.
I don't know who this person
is who's in front of me,
but I'm not agreeing to any of this.
I don't trust them.
And to be honest?
I don't trust you.
Besides, you think anyone
else is gonna want to
sign on to whatever you're selling?
It's not just my vote,
it's the whole class.
You need 2/3.
I already got the signatures.
That's the trick about money.
Banks care more about
it than anything else.
What exactly is in this for you?
You aren't getting the money. I am.
You know that, right?
So I'll ask you one more time.
Why did you come here?
Because you certainly didn't
give a shit about my opinion.
This was just a courtesy.
Two weeks and it's done.
Now this Ray thing got everyone talking.
I didn't have anything to do with that.
Lying ain't your friend right now, cuz.
Everyone got their eyes on you.
Half of them love you.
Half of them want to kill you.
Other half just want
to twist your shit up.
But you know, it's that last half
I'm worried about for you, bro.
Hey.
Little man, book it real quick for me.
I'm good here.
What's that?
Didn't hear you.
You heard.
Fucking
bravery
is contagious.
I suggest you talk to your boy.
He's fine where he is.
Ray's site.
I had 800 Bitcoins in my wallet.
Now, all of a sudden, I got no access.
Can't even make new sales
'cause the site's down.
All of this is on you.
So the way I see it,
you're paying me back.
We'll get some one-on-one
later on.
Just remember, cuz,
sitting under the Sword of Damocles.
Out of the blue,
I received a call from my lawyer.
Seems the contingency
on our biggest lawsuit
was miraculously dropped.
Care to explain?
It's what you wanted, isn't it?
I remember telling you
exactly the opposite.
You just didn't want to ask for it.
But it is what you wanted.
You gonna take the offer then?
Well, it's not for me to say,
officially, but...
despite the fact that
we're hemorrhaging money
at the moment,
settling this would
be a lot cheaper than
dealing with the legal expense.
Can I ask why it was
so important for you
to drop this contingency?
You protecting some
evil, secret agenda?
Aren't we all protecting our
evil, secret agendas?
In that case,
here's mine.
One of the things that Terry Colby
said to me when I took this job
was I could make changes from within.
I want my position moved
to the Risk Management Department.
There's a manager position available.
And even though I may
lack the experience,
I think you know I can
more than make up for it
with drive
and quick learning.
That's how you choose
to squander the capital
you've just earned...
You're aware that's a
lateral move?
It's what I want.
And I am asking.
It's my birthday today.
Did you know that?
No.
Hm.
- I thought...
- No, no...
Don't believe what you read online.
Today
is my actual birthday.
I never share the real one with anyone.
Some things I like to keep to myself.
Happy birthday then.
Would you like to
celebrate
with me?
Tonight?
No.
Well, maybe next year.
Wither thou goest to possess them
and thou succeedest them,
and dwellest in their land.
Amen.
I wanted to tell you I'm sorry.
For my outburst last month.
Can you let go of me, please?
I know you're afraid,
but the fear you have is a right one.
It means you'll be forever vigilant.
You want to know how I know?
I've seen you talking to Him.
Not out loud, but I could tell.
It's written all over your face.
It's not crazy, Elliot,
it's very normal.
You've seen me talking to him?
Yes.
But you don't have to
keep it such a secret.
When you let Jesus into your heart,
He'll always listen.
Tell you what,
I'll give you some alone time.
I need your help.
I've been lost these past few weeks.
Since the whole Ray thing.
I need to finish what I started.
With Evil Corp.
But I don't know what to do.
Why did you first start listening to me?
When I sent you that note
on the server at Evil Corp,
something inside you told you to listen.
And you did.
Followed me off the subway,
came to fsociety,
and then you...
not me...
led us to hack Evil Corp.
I didn't force you to do any of it.
It was all you.
Your choice.
Truth is,
I just followed your lead.
People want to follow you, son.
Why?
Same reason why you led the entire world
into a revolution.
Because you are a leader.
I don't want to be a leader.
You asked me how to finish this.
That's what you need to do.
You need to lead.
And not unlike your floor,
coffee machine, file room.
People in this bullpen, these are your
risk management coordinators,
you'll be working with this team.
Put out risk reports, analyses,
and you report everything out to me.
After Five/Nine, almost all of our time
is dedicated to helping
the crisis response team.
That's what we do here.
Our internal investigation team
make recommendations to management
about ways to
address the crisis and course correct.
Need you to be smart.
Think outside the box and be discreet.
You get in; you get out;
assess the situation quickly;
find answers;
figure out ways to limit damage.
I'm giving you access
to the case we're working on now.
It's a class action
lawsuit brewing in Flint
over water contamination.
Nothing public yet, but
could be big
first quarter, 2016.
Do I just go into the file server
to access that?
I'll have IT
run you through everything.
Setup, Outlook, Calendar.
You knew Gideon Goddard?
We worked together on a couple projects
when he was a vendor.
It's terrible what happened to him.
Well, why don't you go ahead
and get yourself up to speed?
I'll check in once a week.
Let me know if you need anything.
Can I sit in on the
daily debrief meeting?
Look,
that's, uh,
that's a director-level meeting.
We don't really invite managers to that.
If I could just sit and listen
it might help me get up to speed faster.
I want to make sure I can add value
as soon as possible.
All right.
It's later this afternoon.
I'll send you an invite
with the details.
Did you get in
okay this morning with
these protestors out here?
It's crazy, right?
I was on a route to cure
myself of Mr. Robot.
The regiment was supposed
to be that path.
I never thought the
regiment would be the thing
that would lead me right
back where I started.
People always told me growing up that
it's never about the destination.
It's about the journey.
But what if the destination is you?
What if it's always you?
Hey!
Help!
I heard you got a problem.
You know what else your problem is?
Too much courage.
Just like your nigger friend.
He might tell you it's a good thing,
but it ain't always.
It makes you have errors in judgment.
But I'm gonna do you a solid.
I'm gonna fix that courage
problem of yours.
Okay.
We should break that brave,
little soul of yours, homey.
You could've avoided this if
you'd just given me my money.
Think about that.
Think about it.
No, no!
Gonna get a letter on Tuesday.
Do what it says.
Hey, yo, man,
when you see Whiterose,
make sure you say I did you good.
I'll be rooting for you, cuz.
Always.
Usually, they feed us.
It's one of the only reasons
to come to these meetings.
Should we go ahead and start?
It doesn't look like
Susan's gonna make it.
Is there any reason to have
this meeting without her?
The economy must really
be in the shitter
if Susan Jacobs finally decided
to take her vacation days.
First order of business
is the small independent loan
companies we're servicing.
I'm surprised they're not suing us
for breach of the uptime clauses.
I have three class actions on
that point alone in my region.
Contractual damage on
uptime are minimal.
I'm not even worried about it.
We'll settle.
But we should discuss those
when Susan comes back.
Maybe it would be helpful
if I put together a summary
of how we've... handled past cases.
To see if there are any
patterns that might
help us figure out how
to address this issue.
If we pull milestone cases
like Dakota Fracking and
Washington Township,
I could put together a summary briefing.
All I would need is access to the files
and then I could get working
on that right away.
You know what?
There's not much we can do here today.
Food never came, Susan's out.
Let's adjourn.
Didn't I just say that two minutes ago?
We're really leaving before the food?
I said adjourned.
I know who you are.
You did what you did
to get a job here.
You sucked whoever's dick
to get transferred here.
And, frankly, I don't really care.
This is a favor to Price.
You know what he told me,
when I asked him how I
should deal with you?
He said, and I quote,
"However you want."
Enjoy the shrimp cocktail.
This is good news, don't you think?
But you're not happy about it.
I'm not sure.
When did you get it?
This morning.
How are your interactions with him?
For the first time,
we trust each other.
I help him, and he helps me.
Since I've been at my mom's,
I wanted to get rid of him.
But you were right.
You can't destroy a part of yourself.
Elliot, I need to ask you a question.
Where do you think you are right now?
What do you mean?
Elliot,
you know you haven't been staying
with your mother, right?
I know.
When you get released,
I hope you continue
seeing me in my office.
I think it's important we
maintain our regular schedule.
Don't you agree?
Yes.
Mr. Robot was right.
Control can sometimes be an illusion.
But sometimes you need
illusion to gain control.
Fantasy is an easy way to
give meaning to the world,
to cloak our harsh reality
with escapist comfort.
After all,
isn't that why we surround
ourselves with so many screens?
So we can avoid seeing?
So we can avoid each other?
I don't think I'm ready to
talk about it just yet.
So we can avoid truth?
I'm sorry for not
telling you everything.
But I needed this in
order to get better.
Please don't be mad too long.
This will be the last time
I keep things from you.
I promise.
I know what you're thinking,
and no.
I didn't lie to you.
See you in the morning.
All of this really happened.
This was just my way of coping with it.
But now, I'd like it if
we could trust each other again.
Let's shake on it.
- Synca and correctins by Caio -
- www.addic7ed.com -