I don't have many options.
Someone's closing in on us.
I have to find out what they know.
- What exactly are you doing?
- I'm hacking the FBI.
With the FBI at Evil Corp,
physical security is madness.
It's Angela. She's our only option.
- Did you talk to the FBI?
- This is simple.
I'll give you a small device
which you'll take to work.
Drop at the Fed's office on the
23rd floor, and walk away.
We have no other options;
the president can't
go to Congress with a bailout right now.
Let me know when you've
locked up the votes.
What are you up to?
You're not doing anything
on your end to help.
Yo, yo, yo, yo, please buy my CD.
He got into my system
and he wants me to put the CD
on one of the computers at work.
Well, I guess I should pay up, Ahmed,
before I get lynched over here.
Let me guess. You're excited.
Yeah, I'm excited.
We get to go to China.
Elliot, before you get started,
I'm asking you to help me
and not look where you don't need to.
Are we really back to this again?
Ray is not some coffee shop owner.
Forget what you saw and move on.
Hey! Hey!
We're deep down inside you, Elliot.
You can't leave us,
and we can't leave you.
You're watching USA,
America's favorite cable network.
♪ Everybody knows ♪
♪ when the feeling's right ♪
♪ gonna rock the house, it's TV night ♪
♪ get ready ♪
♪ for Word Up Wednesday ♪
What's happening?
Where are we going?
God, Elliot, what's your damage?
Cool it, Darlene.
You know your brother
needs our help sometimes.
That boy of ours.
You sure we're not first cousins?
Where we're going,
Elliot, is a surprise.
Can't say much else.
What I can tell you is,
it's a place that makes
everything better,
a place that changes you.
I should be so lucky.
I have a hunch that you
just might thank me
once we get there.
Why?
What do you mean, why?
This is the annual Alderson
family road trip, that's why.
With all of us together,
taking on the world,
what could possibly go wrong?
What's that sound?
Say, Elliot, what's going
on with you and that girl?
I always liked her. Angela Moss.
Oh, brother, kill me now.
Me and Angela, we're friends.
Ah, I see how it is.
You two are just gonna
keep stringing us along.
Elliot and Angela, a regular
will-they-won't-they couple.
Uh-oh, sounds like that
cancer's acting up again.
Looks like it too.
What is that?
That laughing?
Mom, Elliot's hearing voices.
What else is new?
If you're not careful,
Dad's gonna push you
out a window again.
Pipe down, Darlene.
While I'm alive, you need
to treat me with respect.
I'm your father.
Not for long.
Eyes up, son.
See, on this journey of life,
it's best to stay focused
on the road ahead,
'cause if you spend too
much time looking down,
you might just end up with
a crick in your neck.
- sync and corrections by Caio -
- www.addic7ed.com -
♪ Used to be you could
trust in the story ♪
♪ Vilify the villains and
celebrate the heroes ♪
♪ You could believe in the
guts and the glory ways ♪
Nick of time, huh?
What?
I can feel your bug eyes on me.
Can I see your Game Boy?
No way, you're not allowed.
Your father told you to look ahead.
And you, turn that game down.
Are your fingers broken, young lady?
Not yet, but in this family,
it's only a matter of time.
Ow!
You're burning me.
So what if he hears?
How about being more useful
than your sack-of-potatoes sister?
Mama needs a new pack of Slims.
Lights, remember? I'm
watching my figure.
Somebody help me!
Help!
Somebody!
I'm trapped in here!
I'm here!
- No so fast, kiddo.
- Isn't that...
Nothing but baggage, sorry to say.
No, no, that was Ty...
We're gonna have to get
your peepers checked
as soon as we get home.
In the meantime, go do
what you got to do.
We shove off in five.
I'm sorry.
Hey, no problem, E-meister.
Give me four!
Or not.
Can I help you?
I didn't know you worked here.
Well, I started as a
part-time sales associate.
Then they promoted me
to assistant manager.
Now I'm on pace to be full manager.
It almost makes up for
them killing my mom.
Come on, son. Grab what you can.
Cheez-Its, Pringles, Jolt!
What are you doing?
Elliot, stop him, or I'm
gonna call the police.
Can't worry about her anymore, son.
She's one of them.
No, she's not. She's my friend.
I promise, there are
other fish in the sea.
And if you're anything
like your old man...
On second thought, don't be
anything like your old man.
All right, gang, let's pack
it up and hit the trail.
Together!
Because it's one for Alderson and...
Alderson for one?
You guys'll never believe this.
I just had the most messed-up dream
that Mom slugged me in the face.
I got to get out of here.
Uh-huh, Buster.
Eyes on the road in front of you.
Ouch.
Well, things suddenly
aren't looking so hot
for the Alderson clan.
You screwed up another vacation.
All it not yet lost, gang.
I have a donut.
Just have to get it from
underneath my, uh...
Baggage.
Do you really expect me to believe
there's no one in there?
Elliot, come on. Not
this business again.
You're really starting
to worry me, kiddo.
Did you hit your head
during our little blowout?
Enough of this shit!
Tell me what's happening.
What is this?
Whoa, that doesn't sound good.
On the plus side, I hear
jumpsuits are in these days.
Stay tuned for more Mr. Robot
after this commercial messages.
The Internet is where it's at.
And with E Corp Online the World
Wide Web is better then ever.
News, sports, shopping, and banking.
E-mailing and instant messaging.
All from your own computer.
You can even share photos
with friends and family.
Our new 208k connection lets you
get online in just minutes.
Every day, more and more Americans are
joining the E Corp Online community.
E Corp Online, the future
is just a click away.
If you just asked for a light beer,
Give me a light!
You never know what you'll get.
Dogs! Hah.
Oh actually, Bud Light!
So if you want the clean, fresh
taste that won't fill you up,
and never lets you down,
ask for Bud Light.
- Yours?
- No.
- Give me a light!
- Because everything else...
Showtime!
...is just a light.
Tonight's USA's Up All Night.
Grab your popcorn, it's The Careful
Massacre of the Bourgeoisie.
It all begins tonight,
at 11, on USA Network.
In times of chaos and uncertainty,
when the world feels off balance,
we look to those who've stood with us
from the beginning.
Since 1884, we've had America's back.
We may get knocked down,
but we'll never get knocked out.
We still have your back.
Stay calm, collected.
Follow my lead. It'll always work out.
Car trouble, huh?
He's onto us. Run for it!
Gideon, you're alive.
You folks haven't seen a clan of outlaws
with a kidnapped corporate
exec, have you?
Yikes!
I kill me!
Seem upset, son.
Seriously, Elliot, it's been forever
since that poor cop passed.
It's been 12 seconds.
It's time to move past it.
Future is bright,
endless like that horizon out there.
Whatever you're doing
with me, I don't care.
Just take me back.
It's not that simple, kiddo.
Someone help me!
I'm a businessman!
A very important businessman.
You gonna tell me why you took him?
First you're hearing voices.
Now you're seeing things.
He's right in front of us!
We're staring at him!
Am I the only one here
who isn't batshit?
It'll feel good if you let it.
Believing it's real makes it so.
Come on, grab him by the loafers.
Oh, please, gentlemen.
Ankles instead?
The shoes, they're Ferragamo.
Hyah!
The laughing.
It's a lie.
Sometimes lies can be useful, Elliot.
Sometimes they protect you.
And sometimes they help
you get away with murder.
When the truth is painful, son...
and it often is...
a lie is the only remedy.
'Cause too much truth, too much honesty,
that'll kill ya.
This whole place is a lie.
Nothing here is true.
Listen,
I know your gut's
saying not to trust me.
But look around.
Everything you see,
it's all here for you.
To help you.
You should try just going along with it.
This is it,
isn't it?
You've won.
You've taken over.
What's that, kiddo?
That's what this is.
This road trip.
This family vacation.
I'm buried here.
Well, I'll let you in
on a little secret.
This was never gonna be permanent.
We did always have a destination.
After the beating you took,
at least they got you to a doctor.
You got yourself pretty messed up.
If I were alive, I'd want
no part of that agony.
Nobody's won anything, Elliot,
especially not me.
I'm just trying to help you
put it all in the rearview
as painlessly as possible.
Bring 'er in, kiddo.
Now that the worst is behind you,
it's time we get you back.
Maxine, my dog.
Started to develop a
cough two weeks ago.
She got pretty frail pretty quick.
Fell over a few times.
According to the vet,
she danced with the wrong mosquito,
got herself a...
nasty case of heartworm.
She was moved to a little
room off the basement,
had a water heater for a roommate.
Before she got sick,
Maxine lived like her own operator.
Didn't seem to cross her mind
that she belonged to someone.
But in that basement,
she needed human hands
to give her every scrap of food,
every pill...
Occasional light.
For the first time, she realized
that she continues to breathe
because someone else allowed it,
that she had a master.
Now, I'm no vet,
but I think that realization
might have killed her
before the parasites had a chance.
Anyway, I'ma quit yapping,
let you rest.
Big days ahead.
Work to do.
We can sit here and complain,
or we can go out there
and enjoy ourselves.
I'm gonna sit here and complain.
Well, not everyone enjoys
spending their vacation
in a rain forest.
We're in this rain
forest because of you!
I vote we go home.
You're not voting on this.
Call the newspapers.
Democracy is dead.
It's been two days since
the shocking terror attack
at Beijing's Bayi Lake Hotel,
and while the exact death
toll has yet to be released,
an anonymous source...
Owning the FBI was never gonna be easy.
But now... everyone's on high alert.
We'll be fine.
We only have one day.
You heard what Angela said.
An inter-office email stating
that the FBI's CART team
is vacating E Corp tomorrow.
We don't have a shot
once they're back at the field office.
She'll be ready.
Darlene.
We just started teaching her.
For someone like Angela,
learning all of this in 24 hours
is next to impossible.
Uh... that?
Okay, uh, you know what?
It's... pause.
Maybe you need to... sometimes
it helps to visualize it, okay?
So here.
Your network cable is gonna be plugged
into one of these suckers.
That's a battery-powered
home-brewed mobile tower
called a femtocell.
Now, this guy won't help
us get on the FBI network.
That won't be accessible at E Corp.
What this guy will do is force
every FBI cell phone to connect to it
so it can get every email,
text message, and document.
Now, you SSH in, run the first script.
Period, forward slash,
EnableAttack, space,
femtopwn, space,
WLAN0, comma,
WLAN1, space, two.
No... Uh, that's...
Yeah.
I will get this.
Let's just try it again.
Mm-hmm.
Um...
okay.
This is a Rubber Ducky.
All else fails, you find an FBI
laptop anywhere on the floor.
They're usually Panasonic Toughbooks.
Plug this guy in,
wait 15 seconds, then yank it, okay?
Thanks to a tool called mimikatz,
it'll pull all cached
passwords and domain info in
and save them on this.
Won't give us everything
but might help lead us somewhere.
Just a backup plan.
Okay. Let's try again.
You can't teach someone
to hack in one day, okay?
I don't know how we'll
be ready by tomorrow.
- We need more time.
- Well, we don't have it.
And once they leave E Corp, we're done.
Okay, just keep working on
the scripts with Angela.
Rise and repeat, again and again.
Wax on, wax off.
Do whatever you got to do,
but this is happening.
Okay, the holdup on the femtocell
isn't helping either, okay?
I still need to load the
exploit, need to test it...
It'll be here.
Cisco's still modding
and swapping antennas.
_
Really, man?
I thought we were on the same team.
Wait, wait, wait, wait. No, no, no, no.
What the fuck, Xun?
What the fuck is going on?
Get off me, man! Xun,
what the hell's going on?
Xun, Xun, just wait. The
fuck's going on, man?
What the fuck is going on, man?
Get off me. Get off me.
Fuck, dude.
Get off me, man.
_
No, no, stop, stop, stop. No, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no.
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop!
_
Agent Ramos recommends
four weeks' psych leave.
And you know I don't take
his evaluations lightly.
You were also there.
I was in my room.
I got lucky.
You were smack in the middle.
You owe yourself some time.
I can't go away for a month.
I won't.
We disrupt the investigation,
the Dark Army wins.
Chinese are pointing to a
group of Uighur separatists.
I told you what I saw at the airport.
What you saw doesn't mean anything.
Excuse me, but I disagree.
We were there to investigate the hack,
and then we were under fire.
That is not a coincidence.
By all reports, the Dark
Army are just hackers.
It's not their MO to shoot up a hotel
teeming with FBI.
Violent separatists would
have taken more victims.
I clipped one of the
shooters in the leg.
He went down, hit the floor.
He could have kept firing.
I read the reports, DiPierro.
He turned the gun on himself.
He erased his history.
And the other shooter
actually had me cornered.
I was done.
Swear to God.
But instead, for some reason,
he also put his weapon to his head
and pulled the trigger.
Their mission wasn't to slaughter us.
If it was, I wouldn't be here
arguing with you right now.
They were there to disrupt
our investigation,
to send us home,
and to leave nothing behind.
I don't know what to say.
Everyone's emotional because
of this Beijing thing.
Revenge is on everyone's minds.
The drums of war. I know you hear them.
Be that as it may, Mr. Speaker,
there are ways to drown them out.
With enough passion, people
will buy into anything,
especially at times like these.
The Chinese tied our hands on this one.
If I try to advocate
borrowing from them now,
the American public
will call me a traitor.
And, Phillip, frankly,
I don't even know if I
disagree with them.
Don't shit a shitter, John.
You enter this pissing
contest with China
instead of passing this bailout,
the country goes bankrupt.
Believe me, I would if I could.
A bailout.
No one can make that happen,
not in this climate.
I'm sorry, Phillip.
Minister Zhang's office
has been unreachable.
That cocksucker.
Well, call him again...
and again and again and again.
Don't fucking leave until you get him.
Where's my car?
I'm late for my next appointment.
Sorry, sir.
The driver's having trouble
getting into the parking structure.
Protesters have surrounded the building.
Tell Bratton to summon as
much NYPD as is necessary.
My success is assured.
Um, you know you can't talk to yourself
during the actual operation?
Whatever it takes,
as long as you're almost
ready for liftoff.
We settled on midtown JW?
23rd floor, Eastside View.
This'll be during their lunch hour,
so the floor should be pretty empty.
Okay,
we're officially good to go.
The hell is this?
Nothing.
I thought I recognized your friend,
but I don't.
I'll wait for your
call when I get there.
Jesus.
At least you still got
a few of these left.
I cannot get through a day
in that E Corp building
without juicing, you know what I mean?
Hey, how soon till you re-up on, um...
Everything?
Oh, well, that's it for this place.
I thought I could weather
the storm, but that's...
I can't.
I know it's rough out there,
but you're a survivor, Ahmed.
Yeah, well, not when I
can't pay the rent.
With this cash allowance,
no one's coming in.
No customers, no inventory.
No more of the best damn turkey sandwich
in the tri-state.
Heh.
Man, I'm real sorry.
Yeah. Thanks.
Well, I guess I got to take advantage
while I still can, right?
How about it?
Turkey sandwich on whole wheat.
Oh, yeah, okay.
Lettuce, mayo, Muenster.
Yeah, hi, I'm in room 2301.
I just used my last towel.
I'm running out for a sec but
was wondering if someone
could leave a few extras by my door?
Thank you.
Oh, hi.
Oh, there's no conditioner in my room,
and I'm sure gonna need
it with this humidity.
You know how it is.
Thanks, doll.
Are we still on for lunch?
Yeah, I'll be there.
How's it going?
Shit.
What's up?
The script, it isn't working.
Mobley, are you on?
Yeah, what's on your terminal?
"EnableAttack not found."
Everything okay?
Angela, what's happening?
Angela?
I'm good.
Okay, you have to change your path.
CD, bin, hit Enter.
- Done.
- Now run the script.
And we are live.
Wi-Fi interface is up.
Communicating with femtocell.
Good work.
We're almost there. Do your thing.
Is everything okay?
Who the hell is that?
Yeah.
Fine.
You were in there awhile.
I didn't mean for that to sound weird.
I just noticed because
I've never seen you
on this floor before.
I wanted to make sure
you're all right is all.
We don't have time for this.
Get rid of him.
Anyway, I'm Agent Ross Thomas, CY-5.
Mobley, you're getting the transfers.
Anything?
Angela.
He hails from San Diego,
relationship is complicated.
So what's it like?
Knowing that every room you walk into,
at least one person is quietly
trying to muster the courage
to ask you out.
Jesus, end this before I hurl.
Mobley.
He's been in the bureau
for under a year.
Was infosec before then.
I don't really think about that.
Don't have much yet.
Well, would you think
about drinks with me?
Say, tomorrow night?
I'm actually seeing someone.
Oh, come on. I'm not proposing.
It's one drink.
I won't take no for an answer.
I'm flattered, but I really
have to get back to work.
I've got something.
He calls his mom a weird amount,
and I will exploit that weirdness.
This floor, it's
off-limits to non-bureau.
Did you know that?
I thought you all were moving.
Well? You want to tell
me why you're here?
Shit, Mobley, I'm looking too.
Angela, hold on a sec.
I'm waiting.
So that's all you got?
A little brush-off and you give up?
I just wanted a little flight.
No one's ever handed a win.
What are you doing for lunch?
Busy tomorrow, but...
I can meet you downstairs.
Like, 30?
I know a great Greek
place around the corner.
I'll see you in a half.
All right, you need to find a cubicle
with a network switch under it.
Should be on the ground.
Lots of Ethernet cables
and flashing LEDs.
Found one.
All right, put the battery backup down
and the femtocell next to it.
Plug the battery backup
into a power strip.
Do not unplug the femtocell
from the battery backup.
After that, plug the other end
of the yellow network
cable into the switch.
Don't forget to wipe your
prints from everything.
Okay, the femtocell's plugged in.
You killed it.
Go celebrate.
Shit.
We lost Wi-Fi.
You need to get to a terminal
and bring it back up.
Screw you. I did what you asked.
If we can't get the interface to load,
then we can't use the
Juniper ScreenOS backdoor
to own the network,
which means I can't wipe
the security footage
of you planting the femtocell.
You're fucking kidding me.
Just get to your cubicle.
I'll walk you through it.
Masters. We all have them.
Every relationship's a power struggle.
Some of us need to be controlled.
Once in a while, the
best course of action
is to just ride shotgun.
Stare at the road ahead,
and hope it leads
somewhere you want to go.
There's a USB flash drive in that bag.
When you get to your cubicle,
power off your machine,
plug the flash drive in,
and power it back on.
Hold F12 to bring up your boot options.
Make sure you boot from USB.
Make sure live AMD64 is highlighted,
then hit Enter.
When the desktop comes
up, open a terminal.
Click on the icon of the black screen,
just like you practiced.
Okay, now I need you
to type the following:
SSH, space,
dash L, space,
root, space,
L4713116.e-corp-usa.com.
I lost my place.
The last thing that I entered was three.
116.e-corp-usa.com.
Okay.
Okay, password: joshua.
Homestretch... you're
gonna have to bring up
both Wi-Fi interfaces.
Ifconfig, space,
WLAN0, space, up.
Done.
Last one.
Ifconfig, space,
WLAN1, space, up.
Angela Moss, is that right?
Oh, you in the middle of a call?
I'm sorry.
I hate when people do that to me.
Go ahead. I can wait for you to finish.
Before you get all bent out of shape,
all I was trying to do was
take those punches for you.
That's it.
Thank you.
So if I had to guess,
I'd say you didn't tell
Principal Howard your side?
You know, it's okay to talk about stuff,
to share your side of things.
I'm here to listen.
Always will be.
You don't feel like talking right now,
nobody's gonna force you.
Hopefully you're okay
with listening, though,
'cause...
I actually have something to share,
something I'm pretty embarrassed about.
Mr. Fitch, my supervisor...
you met him, big bald guy,
looks like that guy from "The Simpsons"
that you don't like very much.
A few Fridays ago, he
calls me into his office,
sits me down,
and immediately starts
reading off a list of dates.
September 8th, August 29th, August 2nd.
Few more.
He goes on to tell me that
because of these dates,
my contract is being terminated.
I was being let go.
I asked him why.
He didn't answer.
He just thanked me for
my time, wished me luck,
excused himself, no further explanation.
What were the dates?
They were all appointments
with a doctor.
I had to leave early
for some blood work.
What? What do you mean?
I'm sick, Elliot.
That's what they're telling me.
For a while now.
I've been trying to
keep it from everybody.
Your mom, Darlene,
work, you.
Come on, kiddo.
World isn't gonna get
rid of me that easily.
I'm gonna be okay.
I'm never gonna leave you.
Promise.
Oh, come on.
Enough of this gloom and doom.
Why dwell on the past when we can
take a peek into the future?
The site of my new gig.
That's where I'm taking you.
I'm opening a store...
computers.
Everybody wants to have one.
We love 'em.
Figured it made sense.
You're gonna have a computer store?
Mm-hmm.
Can I work there?
Yeah, don't see why not.
In fact, I will give you your
first assignment right now.
I want you to come up with a name.
What? Stores need a name, right?
I can name it whatever I want?
All right, tell you what.
When we pull up,
the first thing that
comes into your mind,
that'll be the name.
Really?
Now, it's coming up here on the right.
Just keep those eyes on the road.
Now, I don't have the keys yet,
so we can't go in.
I just closed on the place.
It's a bit of a fixer-upper,
but it'll get there.
It's awesome.
Thought you'd like it.
Hey, uh, back there,
what we talked about,
let's just keep that between us, okay?
Don't even tell your mom.
Just our little secret.
Good.
Now, you have work to do.
This place needs a name.
Now, remember,
the first thing that
pops into your mind.
- sync and corrections by Caio -
- www.addic7ed.com -