You brought me in to manage him,
and that's exactly what I've done.
I'm going to get him
a job at Evil Corp.
Doesn't hurt to have him
on the inside.
I'm sending
shipping requests
to the actual facilities,
but in the manifest,
I'm making it look like all the paper
is still arriving in New York.
How do you bring justice
to a conglomerate
as untouchable as Evil Corp?
ANGELA; When I met Whiterose,
she opened my eyes,
and I could see how
all of the damage
that they've caused
could finally be undone.
No!
Don't you see it yet?
We are gods.
What's that for?
In case Elliot comes back.
He sometimes can become
a different person.
Answer me!
Stay away from
me, you fucking psycho.
I like what you did
with the place.
Still like mine better though.
You ever think about
not doing this shit anymore?
Can't we just be a normal couple
that complains about the water bill,
looks up vacation packages
to Budapest?
Hello, E Corp.
Guys back at CART are
zeroing in on the guy in the video.
We might have
a good lead soon.
Your job is to get intel
from Elliot on Tyrell Wellick.
That is the only reason
you're not in jail right now.
Good job. You get anything
from Elliot's computer?
Last night he sent an
encrypted e-mail with a link.
DiPIERRO: Is
that coming from downstairs?
Is Darlene home?
Hey.
I said "hey."
What's your deal?
Come on, dude,
I don't have all day.
What do you want?
Come on, look around you.
The entire train is either
asleep or drop-dead exhausted.
Meanwhile, you're over here
riverdancing,
trying way too hard to pretend
like you're in a hurry
to get somewhere we both know
you don't have to be.
Honestly, I don't know
what you're saying.
You have my wallet.
You're batshit.
And you're a terrible
pickpocket.
Take out my wallet.
Take it out, now.
Open it.
There should be a Polaroid
inside. Take it out.
Look, I didn't take anything.
Just take it back.
Take out the Polaroid.
Was that so hard?
Thank you.
Wait, what is this? Don't you
want your wallet back?
It's yours.
Why'?
You stole from me,
but I stole from you first.
That old lady knitting,
that frat dude over there,
I stole from them too.
Everyone.
This whole economic
fuckshow is my fault,
and everything that's happened
to you and everybody else
since Five/Nine,
that's my bad too.
That's not even
the cherry on top.
I killed a woman.
Got her right in the heart
with a stun gun.
This is me.
Wait!
Metadata.
The story behind the data.
Getting information
is one thing,
but how it was created,
where and by whom
can often be illuminating.
NORM; Who the fuck is that?
Is Darlene home?
No, she's out.
This e-mail wasn't for Tyrell.
It was for us.
Fuck me sideways,
how did he know?
He must've phished us
when you went to that URL.
Shit, shit, Shit.
Should we bring him in?
What if Darlene gets back?
Like most pics people
post on Instagram or Facebook,
they don't realize
they just gifted
whatever social media site
their camera type,
phone model, name,
and location,
all hidden inside
the photograph's metadata.
Come on, Darlene,
pick up the goddamn phone.
Jesus H.
She left her phone downstairs.
How long ago did she leave?
Doesn't matter. She's back.
It's over. Our lead asset
is about to get burned.
Let's bring him in. This guy's
time is past due anyway.
I never trusted his bug eyes.
If we do that, it'll burn
Elliot's bridge to Tyrell.
It's about to be burned
anyway.
Where are you going?
Don't look at me. Act normal.
Elliot phished us.
He's in your apartment.
Stay cool,
don't blow your cover.
You said
you were leaving town.
What are you doing here?
Since when do you have
an apartment?
How can you afford this place?
None of your fucking
business. Leave.
I told you to walk away
from this.
And I told you to leave. We clearly
have communication issues.
Let's go.
You're coming with me.
We have to talk.
Not gonna happen.
I am not going
anywhere with you.
Last night, I noticed
some extra hardware
wired to my monitor's
display controller
along with a small cellular
modem taking screen shots
every ten seconds and sending
them out somewhere,
and now I'm standing here,
and I wanna know
why the fuck are you
hacking me?
Take another step,
and I will fucking scream.
You're not gonna
hurt me again.
And if it is him
that I'm talking to right now,
then yeah, I hacked you.
I don't trust you,
so back the fuck off.
Darlene...
It's me.
Yeah, well, that's a pretty
complicated statement
coming from you.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
Dom, get back here now.
Audios useless.
He's using a goddamn
voice protector.
You should've listened to me.
He is still here, and you
can't keep ignoring it.
Doesn't mean you hack me.
We don't do that
to each other.
You wouldn't talk to me. What
else was I supposed to do?
He's working with them,
isn't he?
I need to show you something.
Mm.
I know, I know,
ribs for breakfast,
but I can't pass 'em up
when I'm here.
You know,
the key is in the moisture.
Here, look.
See that pink in there'?
Red Wheelbarrow understands.
Mop sauce,
that's their secret.
Layman's version,
two tablespoons dry rub
to one cup
apple cider vinegar,
maybe beer, depends.
Then use a brush
to mop the ribs
during the cooking process.
Delicious.
You said we needed to talk.
Anyone tail you
on the way here?
SD Rs are now
second nature to me.
Did three cover stops,
nothing.
Oh, good.
Well, this is just a little
Monday morning
staff meeting update
kind of thing.
Today's Friday.
It was a figure of speech.
Point is I received
official word.
We go on September 29th,
ten days from now.
Now, you know how the boss
feels about timetables.
You said you can manage
those two knuckleheads,
and she put a lot
of faith in you.
I'm assuming you can make
this happen.
What about the shipping
delays?
Well, good thing we have
our guy on the inside, huh'?
Help speed things up.
Of course.
We'll make it happen.
Good.
I wanna be sure too.
We've prepared
for an emergency evacuation
so no one will be
in the building when we go'?
I'm asking.
We have.
Keep us on schedule,
all will be good.
I have to ask...
did Whiterose ever show you?
YES.
And you believe in it?
Take a look at technology
nowadays.
It's mind-boggling.
Hell, these ribs.
You think it was even possible
to cook 'em as deliciously
as this a 100 years ago?
I mean, who knows
if this is even real meat?
As tasty as they are, I wouldn't be
surprised if they grew 'em in a lab.
I'm not talking about ribs.
My point is, I think
anything is possible.
Did he do this, or...
No, it was me.
I had to do a deep search,
make sure no one
was listening.
You were right.
Stage 2 was never called off.
ls Tyrell involved?
Has to be.
They're still trying to blow
up the recovery building.
I've been monitoring
traffic at E Corp,
and that led me
to an unpatched web server.
Talk to me.
I'm trying to show you.
Ifs all right here
in my research.
Why are you monitoring them?
You could've taken
all of this,
sent it in as an anonymous tip
and walked away.
It's not that simple.
Yes, it is.
You don't want
to turn them in.
Why'?
Tell me what's going on.
I want to be the one
that finds them.
I need to see
where this leads.
What does that mean?
Elliot, listen to me.
This is not who you are.
You don't blow up buildings.
You don't hurt people.
I know.
What is this, then?
There's something inside me that
can't let go of what we started.
What we started is over.
Before, when I was here, you
said you wanted to stop this.
I need you to go back
to that place.
Tell me right now,
can you do that?
YES.
Good.
So with that in mind
and with what you have,
how do we find them and just
end this once and for all?
The best lead we've got is me.
She gave me her keys
when we were...
Landlord never changed
the locks,
and it's been vacant.
So what? You just...
come in here and hang?
I get it.
I haven't lost time
during the day,
but at night...
That's when you want me
to stay awake and keep watch
on the off chance
you turn into Mr. Hyde
and follow you to Tyrell
and the Dark Army.
Hey.
You're my brother.
I'm always here for you.
Besides, if you really think this
is the best way to find Tyrell...
it's weird, but I guess we passed
weird a long fucking time ago.
I'm in.
Shit, I have to get to work.
Whatever he does,
it's not me.
I know.
Come in.
The last thing anyone wants
is some...
sleazy politician...
Oh, please, come.
It'll be great.
No, I...
How far is this place?
Just around the corner.
Oh, right,
well, I just wanted to say...
Thank you
for the Christmas card.
You're welcome.
Look, I'm so sorry
about that day.
I came into the room,
and he slinked towards me,
and there was a fire, and he's the
President of the United States,
and nothing happened.
I promise.
And I just felt like
such a fool because...
FBI, FBI! FBI!
On your fucking knees!
Hands behind your head!
Stay right there.
Don't you fucking move!
Don't move.
Don't you fucking move.
I sometimes wonder
if I'd died
when Tyrell shot me,
would my revolution
have died with me?
At first, I thought
the Dark Army saved my life.
They didn't though.
They saved him, Mr. Robot.
And now he's trying to wage
a terrorist attack,
and that excites me.
Why?
Darlene's right.
I could've tipped off the FBI,
given them all this evidence
and let them handle it.
I could just go back to my
new TV and IKEA furniture.
What's wrong with me?
ANGELA; What's that?
Nothing, boring.
It's a scan, encrypt, archive.
It's the new consolidation.
Meetings next week, I think.
That was a terrible lie.
There's no way
she believes me.
Okay.
You're still coming
to the party tonight, right?
I forgot that part
of being a corporate drone
is going to mandated
office functions.
Yeah, definitely.
I wouldn't miss it.
Great.
One of these days, you gotta
pound that ass, dude.
Like, I've been out here
splashing everything in sight,
but it's starting to feel
a little lonely in p-town.
Don't let her slip away,
all right?
I need you on this.
DiPIERRO: We know you posted
the fsociety video.
With a court order, we got
the Vimeo connection logs
for the account you used,
which led us
to your IP address
and then your home address.
That's why
you're sitting here.
What my partner's trying to say
is you're on a path to a hell,
and we're not talking
the thousand virgins kind.
We're talking sharing
a prison shower
with a few Allah-hating Nazis
on the daily.
You're young.
Don't waste these years
behind bars.
All you gotta do is tell us
who's behind this.
Do you know Darlene Alderson?
Elliot Alderson,
do you know him?
Have you ever worked with him?
Tyrell Wellick,
is he your leader'?
The tough, quiet kind.
Boys in Gitmo find
your type especially cute.
White rose.
Is Whiterose your leader?
Mr. Nouri, when I get bored,
I get very teed off,
and this silent treatment of
yours is a straight-up sedative.
So this is the last time
I'm gonna ask you,
and I urge you this time,
do not bore me.
Who is your leader?
Fsociety.
Just me.
Could have fooled me.
What's with the Armani
Exchange getup?
I came from a work party.
Copy that.
You good for the night?
You sure you can stay up'?
Just did an eight ball,
so I'm golden.
Maybe we should have
some sort of signal
when I'm coming and going
so you know it's me.
How about you just tell me?
That's a good signal.
Good night.
Wait, are you going to sleep?
I was gonna walk
Flipper first.
Cool, I'll come with.
Okay, so, just thinking
out loud, but...
if I do follow him
and find Tyrell
and the Dark Army
and shit goes down,
like, bad shit,
you'd get vengeance, right'?
Like, if I die or something,
you'll kill whoever did it,
and, obviously,
I'll do the same for you.
Like, like a vengeance pact.
Is that even a thing?
It can be our thing.
You in?
Fuck yeah, I'm in.
Cool.
Darlene...
I'm sorry.
I treated you like shit
for weeks.
I shouldn't have been
pushing you away.
You're my fucking sister.
I should've believed you.
We've got the fsociety
video traced
right to that asshole's
apartment.
We got more than half the FBI
across the country
chasing Tyrell Wellick,
and you're asking that yahoo
about the mythical Whiterose from
the land of Dark Web Fairy Tales?
Come on, Dom, Whiterose is a boogie
man story for the Dark Army.
Groups like these
don't have leaders.
The Dark Army isn't like
any other group.
And I'm tired of being the only one that
questions their involvement in this.
No doubt they're involved, but this
video is fsociety to the bone,
and ever since
we picked up our guy,
fsociety chatter
is off the charts.
Makes sense if they're planning
to make good on their threat,
and we just snagged
one of their operatives.
This guy practically
handed us his location.
I don't like it.
Okay, but isn't every
Dark Army member
trained to pull a trigger on
themselves in lieu of getting caught?
Why'd he surrender?
I checked
with the other facilities.
Elliot's been rerouting the
shipments all over the country.
No, no, no, no, no, no!
Why am I even surprised?
I told you this would happen.
You know him.
You know he can't be trusted.
He's behind
the shipping delays.
This explains everything.
This manifest
was a fucking mirage.
And on top of that, you've
agreed to a new timeline?
That was before
I knew about all of this.
I came here to talk about
our options.
Options? We have no
fucking options!
What happened
to your perfect plan?
You placed him at E Corp to speed up
the consolidation, not to stop it.
We're worse off
than where we started.
Why did you even let him
work there in the first place?
It was the best way
to manage him.
This doesn't change anything.
This can still be salvaged.
This is all your fault.
No, it's all his fault.
The Dark Army needs to know
what he's done.
You know that you can't
tell them.
You understand
the consequences.
And not just for Elliot,
for all of us.
Well, maybe I can reason
with them.
Never appeal
to a man's better nature.
He may not have one.
This isn't impossible.
We arrange to have
the western-most states
ship their records by plane.
Our trucks will handle
the East Coast.
We just need to stay focused.
Everyone will notice the trucks.
It will draw too much attention.
If we move the paper
over the weekend,
we can operate
under the radar.
In the meantime, I'll have
Elliot's access revoked
to make sure that he doesn't
interfere again.
What?
You can promise
this motherfucker
won't stop us again when he
wakes up in the morning?
You can talk to me.
Okay.
Face it, Elliot, if that's who
I'm even talking to.
We work nights together for over
six weeks to prepare this project,
but you spend your days ruining
all we've accomplished.
You, as a person, make no sense.
You're a liability.
Our goal hasn't changed.
I can't follow
this back-and-forth anymore.
You had one simple directive.
To maintain control
until the plan was executed.
It doesn't work that way.
There's no on/off switch.
Then tell me,
how does it work?
'Cause I don't even know which
Elliot I'm talking to right now.
How it works is I am here now.
Don't forget
whose operation this is.
I once thought
you to be a God.
I loved you.
But now I see how foolish I
was and how inferior you are.
Like a fucking cockroach.
You messed up
for the last time.
I'm taking over. So, no.
This is no longer
your operation.
This is mine.
Listen to me,
you Swedish scumfuck.
This is my revolution.
I am the architect.
Do you understand?
The only reason you are here
is because
I allowed you to be.
Don't forget I could've
pulled that trigger twice.
He is fucking crazy.
I want him out, out!
He's unfit to run this op.
YOU Okay?
Hey.
Look me in the eyes and
tell me that you're okay.
Shit.
What's happening?
He's here.
Angela?
Why is he here?
Hey, it's okay.
What are you doing?
Calm down.
Where am I?
Everything's gonna be...
Please tell me
you know what's happening.
It's okay.
Just tell me
you know what's happening.
Please, tell me you know
what's happening.
Tell me you know
Tell me you have something.
Buy me a drink.
I've been covering your ass
the last week.
You disappeared.
All I've gotten is one text
saying you might have
a development,
and now you want me
to buy you a drink?
You almost got me busted
by my own brother, remember'?
Yeah, I'm still butthurt about
that, in case you were wondering.
And you never told us
what you two talked about
when he came
to the safe house.
Yeah, well, maybe I'm just
tired of being a traitor.
Maybe I just wanna be
a normal person
for one fucking minute, okay'?
So how about you buy me...
a drink?
You know I could get in trouble for
meeting up with you like this,
one-on-one?
You're supposed to be
at the safe house.
Yeah, well,
we tried it your way,
and Elliot ended up
almost making us.
Okay, now we're trying it
my way.
What'll you have?
Bourbon, Eagle Rare, neat.
On her tab.
Okay, you got your drink.
Now tell me what else you got.
You said you're from Jersey.
What part?
I don't have time
for Q and As.
My way, remember?
I need to know what you have.
Well, I'll tell you
what I don't have.
I have no friends.
I have no social contact.
I have no life because of you.
Now, you said
you're from Jersey.
You don't fucking say.
What part?
The world-renowned town
of Teaneck.
Siblings?
Two brothers.
Relationship status?
How many of these do I have
to go through?
Relationship status?
Okay'...
On again off again
with someone,
but they're not really the one
or anything like that.
Ah...
The old pronoun game.
I experimented
with that for a bit.
It's all good with me.
Thanks for your approval.
Ifs 2015 now.
Why the coded dialog'?
FBI doesn't approve
of muff-divers?
Let's just say
it keeps things simple.
Whatever diddles your skittle.
What about you?
Well, my last relationship
didn't end very well.
You were there, remember'?
Shit.
This is why
I don't do the social thing.
Darlene, I get
this is tough for you.
We've got a lot of intel
that says something
is happening and soon.
From the looks of it,
it could be big.
We need to get Tyrell
before it's too late,
which means you need to tell
me if you know something.
I think I have a lead,
but I need to go at it alone
without a wire.
That's not gonna happen.
Well, tough titties, it's the
only way I'm doing this.
Because when I do this,
and you're all popping Cristal
after you land Tyrell,
understand something...
it's game over for me.
I may have immunity,
but I'm gonna lose my brother.
No can do, Kathmandu.
This needs to happen
by Monday.
But I can't work with him
anymore.
Elliot is dead to me.
Our partnership is over.
Uh-huh, and...
Shipping paper records
from 71 buildings
across the country to New York
over this weekend?
It would draw too much
attention.
That sounds like a YP,
not an MP.
I don't know what to tell you.
Whiterose is strict
about her schedule.
Be reasonable.
I'm back at the beginning.
Give me more time.
As I said, has to happen
on Monday.
Why the change in deadline?
You knew there were delays.
This mad rush isn't worth
the risk.
You keep squawking as if I'm gonna
give you a different answer.
Look, you get this done,
we all take a nice vacation.
I've been looking for some
time to finish my book.
You don't understand.
I lost my partner.
We were supposed to be gods
together, but it's over.
Tyrell, I get that you
and Elliot are having...
interpersonal issues.
Sometimes coworkers find
that they aren't the right fit
but they still gotta finish
the job, you know?
Besides, you and I both
know this has nothing
to do with Elliot being a god.
If he is no longer with you,
if he cannot finish the job,
well, that proves one thing.
You are the god, not him.
And I am damn confident
that you will find a solution
to our timing issue.
You were destined
for this, Tyrell.
This is your moment.
This is the moment
you were born for.
You cannot turn away now.
YES.
There is a way.
First, the baby monitor.
I haven't been able
to connect in weeks.
They must've set up
a new system.
Regardless, I want to see them
in person instead.
My wife, my son, and I
will go to the Ukraine,
together,
on Monday after the plan
is complete.
They don't extradite
to the U.S.
I want your word.
I'll get into that.
Okay.
Do me a favor
and check on Joanna.
I've been reading online,
and it seems
she's been maintaining
a low profile.
Make sure she's okay
and inform her of the plan.
Of course.
And Irving?
There's one last thing I need
in order to execute.
What's that?
The full force
of the Dark Army.
Your message said
this was urgent.
I'm coming to you because I don't
have just cause for this request,
But I need it
to happen quickly.
Go on.
I need you to fire
Elliot Alderson.
Ban him from any and all
E Corp branches
and subsidiaries.
And why do you want me
to fire him?
I have my reasons.
Explaining them won't help,
but my discretion on them
is important to me.
And you're comfortable
making this decision?
Mr. Price, I know this random
employee doesn't matter to you.
He's just a number.
You can continue
to question me
because you seek
my true reasons,
or you can deny my request
because I'm overreaching.
But I'll return the favor.
You know I'm good for it.
If you want my reasons,
I'll have to restate
what I said.
They are mine,
and my discretion on them
is important.
And this is your request?
It is.
Consider it done.
Thank you.
You still there?
Yes, it's me.
Relax, I said it's me.
How are you feeling?
Are you gonna tell me
what happened?
We've been over this.
Elliot saw everything.
I had to knock him out,
and now we're here.
I was asking
about your phone call.
We're good to go.
Price said yes,
but you're staying here
this weekend.
Can't have any more
accidents.
He's gonna wake up again.
He saw you and Tyrell.
He only saw us
for a few seconds.
Maybe he won't remember.
And, if he does,
I'll handle it.
You just do what you do best.
Fight him off.
I told you
this would happen.
I told you that he would
find a way to stop us.
Stage 2 has been
completely derailed.
What is it?
Irving.
He says we'll be ready
to go on Monday.
Open up.
Any day, dude, it's me.
Elliot?