Seventy one buildings
exploded or caught fire.
Elliot, tell me what
it is that you think he did.
Sorry. I don't know
if I can say.
No matter what happens now,
everything will be fine.
I should be at home
with my family.
My brother is probably
flipping out right now.
I'll be back later.
What do normal people
do when they get this sad?
I do morphine.
If what I discovered is real,
do you know what that means'?
We can potentially
undo this whole thing.
Everything in this room
is only here to tell a story.
If anything
does happen to us...
If I don't make it
back to my computer,
I sent the email to go out
automatically.
No, don't do this!
Stop!
To someone I trust.
Your dad pushed you
out a window?
Broke my arm.
Went to the hospital.
I was angry.
I hated myself.
It's okay. I'll get it
out of my system
before the movie.
Don't you worry.
Here.
All right.
Dump them on in there.
Come on.
You know what to do.
Come on, kiddo.
Shake 'em up.
What? You don't want any?
Told you I didn't wanna come.
I know, but...
It's movie night.
Is it the movie?
I thought you wanted to see
Shallow Grave.
I hear it's pretty good.
Um...
Maybe we could see this,
Jerky Boys thing.
Maybe it's not sold out yet.
I wanna go home.
How long are you
gonna be mad at me?
I told you I was sorry.
You're not sorry.
You're just sick and
don't want to admit it.
You're right.
I made some mistakes.
I wish I could have been
a better father to you.
All I'm asking is
that you'll forgive me.
Do you think you'll ever
be able to do that?
No.
Yeah.
Maybe we should leave.
Oh' my!
Somebody call 911!
The movie's about to start.
Welcome. Your
movie will begin shortly.
Please keep our theaters clean
by disposing of your trash in
the specified waste containers.
Food and refreshments
are available in the lobby.
Gift certificates
are also available
on special occasions.
Sit back, relax,
and enjoy the show.
When you delete something,
you're making a choice
to destroy it.
To never see it again.
You choose to delete because
you need to free up space.
Because you don't
want it anymore.
Because it no longer
holds value.
Is that what happened
to Mobley and Trenton?
Were they unwanted?
Taking up too much space?
You can't keep doing this. What?
Why did you wipe-down?
Routine.
You need to talk to Angela.
She is not doing well.
Last time I saw her,
she was going through
a full-on breakdown.
I don't care.
She should be
breaking down.
Nice.
I recall her
being there for you
when you had
your little episode.
Multiple times.
Guess I'm an asshole.
It's been three weeks.
You haven't left
your apartment.
I'm getting worried
about you.
Don't.
What happened
with the attacks,
that's not you.
Even if it was him,
it was me.
How do you even know
he did this?
What does it even matter,
Darlene?
He got what he wanted.
Didn't he?
Except, wait a minute. Nope.
E Corp's still gonna be
just fine because of Ecoin.
He sure didn't see
that coming, did he?
Whoops! Oh, well.
Consolation prize,
at least we get to be
miraculously off the hook
for everything.
Yes, sure, a couple of good people
had to die in disgrace for that.
But who's counting
at this point? Am I right'?
I mean, I'm sure he's just
doing fucking dandy.
If that's what this is about,
you can still get rid of him.
You don't get it.
I tried everything.
The medication, therapy...
Fuck, I even put
myself in jail.
He won't leave.
He won't leave
because I wanted this.
I liked ii.
Fuck you.
You're really scaring the
shit out of me right now.
I'm not trying
to scare you.
I just...
Just give me some time.
I need to find my own way
to cope with this.
I don't believe you.
I feel like...
I feel like
you're giving up.
Just let me
stay with you.
Okay, that'll make me
feel better. Please.
I just wanna be alone.
Give me some time. Okay?
I tell you what.
You come by tomorrow,
we'll smoke up,
and we can watch
Careful Massacre.
It's not even Halloween.
Since when did we start
following the rules?
I'd like that.
Me too.
Just for the day. You'd
be doing me a big favor.
Of course.
She's practically family.
I'll bring her toys and food over.
She likes this purple
eggplant thing.
I know. You, left it here
the last time.
And I got food left over,
so we're good for the day.
Deletion.
When you make that decision,
there's always that
moment of hesitation.
That annoying, "Are you
sure?" dialog box.
And then you
have to make a call.
Yes or no.
Yes means ridding myself and the
world of Mr. Robot forever.
That includes you.
There you go.
Thanks.
Next?
Maybe it's something I
should have done a long time ago.
Thanks.
Next.
This is Hard Andy's
pure grade,
top shelf,
all-name-brand supply.
No knock-offs or generics.
This is all straight from
the pharma's assembly line.
You got Addys, Exies,
Black Beauties, Oxies,
Xannies, Roxis...
Morphine.
Miss Emma.
She's good.
Those come straight from the manufacturing
plant in Jersey. Like I said,
Hard Andy's supply
is always clean.
Pure as a nun's cunt.
I'll take it.
Perfect.
Let me get you a bottle.
The whole bag.
That's my whole stash.
Then you just made
an easy sale.
Refresh my memory.
How do we know
each other, again?
Referral. We got
a friend in common.
Take off your shirt.
Come on, man.
You just did
a pat-down outside.
I said take off
your fucking shirt.
See, people don't
usually come in here
trying to buy
Hard Andy's whole stash
unless one of three
prerequisites are met.
One, they got their nose
up some fuzz's ass
which we will soon ascertain.
Pants, also.
Two, you're trying
to resell in my market.
But... you don't strike me
as a dummy with a death wish.
Spin around.
Which leaves three.
Life that unbearable, baby'?
Cute little boy like you.
The pleasure
I could give you.
Such a shame.
Maybe you do have
that death wish after all.
What do you want?
I was a friend
of your brother, Mobley.
I mean, Sunil.
Get lost, man.
Wait.
I just wanted to pay
my respects.
I was wondering if you could
tell me where I should go.
That fat fuck doesn't deserve
respect from anyone.
Do you know how much
he's damaged my career?
My firm is on the verge
of firing me.
I get that you're going
through a lot.
But don't believe the lies
you read about him.
They're not true.
It's been all over the news.
What, do you think they just
make this shit up now?
The facts are there.
He was working
with the Iranians.
And I have no doubt he got lured
into some bullshit like that.
He's been a fuck-up
his whole life.
I just want to know where
I can go to say a few words.
Your guess is
as good as mine.
There's no way I was gonna pay
for a terrorist's funeral.
This is a reminder
that today's city-wide curfew
begins at 9:00 p.m.
this evening
through 4:00 a.m.
tomorrow morning.
Stay indoors
and off the streets.
This is a reminder
that today's city-wide curfew
begins at 9:00 p.m.
this evening
through 4:00 a.m.
tomorrow morning.
Stay indoors
and off the streets.
Are you moving?
Are you leaving the city?
Please, sir.
We don't want any trouble.
I'm not here to give you
any trouble.
I just wanted to talk.
Please, we just want
to leave in peace.
I went to school
with your daughter.
I wanted to say
she was a good person.
What do you want from us?
I want you to know
she's innocent.
I'm sorry, how did you know
my daughter, again?
Did you speak with her
before she left?
Do you know why she went
to Arizona?
No.
I just know her.
I know she
wouldn't do this.
Shama was a victim.
Somebody did this to her.
This country now blames
Muslims for everything.
There's no room
for us here anymore.
Thank you for saying nice
things about my daughter.
MOHAMMED;
That's a lot of pills.
Are you sick?
What are you doing here?
What are you doing here'?
Where are your parents?
Who cares?
I don't need
a babysitter.
Go home.
Leave me alone.
I don't know
how to go home.
What do you mean? Just go
back the way you came.
Where did I come from?
Go down the street.
Take the train.
I don't know
how to do that.
Well, how did
you get here'?
I followed you.
What are you doing?
Sitting here.
You don't own the beach.
Are you serious, man?
Your parents are probably
really worried about you.
Hold you. I don't
need a babysitter.
Besides,
I don't wanna go home.
Why do you think my sister
didn't do anything wrong?
Dude, you can't
just stay here.
Come on.
Come with me.
You sure
this is a shortcut?
It's the
way we always go.
My sister used to take me
this way after prayer.
Our mosque
is on the way.
Where do you pray?
I don't.
You're lucky.
It's so boring,
and your face is always
up another guy's butt.
At the mosque,
Shanna used to trip
whenever she put
her shoes back on.
I can do it while standing
and not fall down.
You wanna see?
No.
That's awesome.
Can you do it'?
Probably.
You sure this is the fastest
way to your home?
I gotta get back
to Coney Island.
Why'?
Because I have
something to do.
What?
It's personal.
Like what?
Let's talk about
something else.
Like what?
Don't worry about it.
Why?
This is a reminder.
Today's citywide curfew begins at 9:00 p.m.
this evening
through 4:00 a.m.
tomorrow morning.
Where are your parents?
They usually leave me home
alone when they go out.
The door locks
automatically.
Do you have a phone?
I wish.
Do you know their number?
Their phone number.
I don't know.
Today's citywide curfew
begins at 9:00 p.m. this evening
through 4:00 a.m.
tomorrow morning.
Do you like TV?
No.
Do you like horses?
Do you like Wii U?
No.
Do you like movies?
I used to.
I've never been
to the movies.
My parents say
it's too expensive.
That sucks.
Would you take me?
Take you where?
To the movies. Duh.
No. Can't take you
to the movies.
I told you I have
something I gotta do.
Besides, there's probably
nothing good playing.
If your parents come home
and see that you're missing,
they'll probably
call the cops.
How far away did they go?
Are they close?
Dan bury.
In Connecticut?
That's two hours away.
My uncle lives there.
He likes to live by the mall.
He's bald.
This is serious.
I can't sit here
for two hours.
That's what I'm telling you.
We should go to the movies.
Are you lying to me just
so I take you to the movies?
No.
We're only going if
something good is playing.
What's Back to the Future?
Can we see
The Martian instead?
Are you kidding?
First of all, The Martian
looks like shit.
Second of all, you've never
seen Back to the Future?
No. It looks like an old movie.
You don't understand.
Today's the day that Marty
travels into the future.
I've wanted to see
this movie on this day
since I was your age.
So weird that it's today.
Why?
It won't make sense to you. Why?
What are you doing?
You just ruined it.
This is the best way
to eat popcorn.
Trust me.
Wow. That's good.
No shit. Come on.
So, what is this film
about, anyway?
It's hard to explain.
Ifs about going
into the future
to change the past,
then coming back into an
alternate present day.
No, you can't go into the
future to change the past.
Ifs way heavier
than that.
He goes into the future
to change the future.
But that allows Biff
to change the past,
which changes
the future again.
No, no, it's much
simpler than that.
It's about how one mistake
can change the world.
Now seating for
Back to the Future Part ll.
Are you sure we can't
see The Martian?
Come on.
You're gonna love it.
But The Martian has 92%
on Rotten Tomatoes.
That's because most critics
have shitty taste.
Excuse
the disguise, Marty,
but I was afraid
you wouldn't recognize me.
Would you mind holding my
Flux Capacitor for a second?
I... I gotta clean
my glasses.
Changed the blood, added a
good 30 to 40 years to my life.
They also replaced
my spleen and colon.
What do you think?
You look great, Doc.
The future. Unbelievable.
I gotta check this out, Doc.
Ah' in good time, Marty.
Were on a tight schedule here.
Tell me about my future.
I mean, I know I make it big,
but what do I become, like,
a rich rock star?
Please, Marty.
No one should know too much
about their own destiny.
Right, right-
I am rich, though, right?
Marty, please.
Take off your shirt.
Put on the jacket
and shoes.
We've got a mission
to accomplish!
Hey, come on, dude.
Have you seen a little boy
like this tall?
Blue hoodie?
Yeah.
He peaced out.
These heels
are the pits.
I should have gone
as 1955 Lorraine.
Ow.
What? Try me.
I'm looking for a mosque.
It's near a playground.
Masjid Al Rahman
or The Islamic Society?
Come on, we'll figure it out.
I have good friends
in both places. Come on.
What are you waiting for?
Get in.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I have a grave announcement
to make.
Incredible as it may seem,
both the observations
of science and the evidence
of our eyes lead
to the inescapable assumption
that those strange beings
who landed in the Jersey
farmlands tonight
are the vanguard
of an invading army
from the planet Mars.
War of the Worlds, huh?
Why not?
'Cause it's about the end
of the world.
No, that's incorrect.
Things get a little fakakta
for a while,
but at the end,
humans actually persevere.
Monstrous creatures
in the world now seems
part of another life.
A life that has no continuity
with the present.
Why did you bail on me
at the theater?
I would have come here with
you, if that's what you wanted.
No, you wouldn't.
You keep saying you have
something you have to do.
I do have something to do.
Now come on.
We're going back.
Why did you come
to our house?
Yo, this isn't cool, okay?
I gotta go.
Is it that important?
Yes.
Why'?
It's none of your business.
You're a baby.
You're annoying.
You are!
This is a nightmare.
So are you!
I wish you were dead!
So do I!
Sometimes I feel like I...
Did something bad
that made Shama leave.
You didn't do
anything wrong.
All right.
I'm gonna give you five.
And then we're gonna go.
I'm not going anywhere.
Just leave me alone.
It wasn't your fault.
Or hers.
It was mine.
All of it.
So don't blame her
or yourself.
You can blame me.
You know, you talk about
yourself a lot.
And you're not allowed
to wear shoes here.
I'm not gonna trip
when I put them back on.
We'll see.
Did you know I could be
President of the United States?
Yeah?
My sister couldn't be.
She wasn't born here.
My mom and dad
couldn't, either.
I'm the only person in my
family who could be President.
Isn't that cool?
If I were President...
I would be able
to stay here.
In the house we live in.
I would find a way
to bring back my sister.
I'd put the real
bad guys in jail.
And... And I'd make everyone
eat Pop Tarts for dinner.
And then make everyone
be nice to me.
So you'd be a dictator.
What's a dictator?
Ifs like a really
bad President.
Can you be President?
Probably not.
So you're like my sister?
You weren't born here?
No, I was.
Where?
New Jersey.
Really? Me too.
What part?
Washington Township.
Where were you born?
Trenton.
Looks like your parents
still aren't home.
You had the keys
this whole time?
Thanks for taking me
to the movies.
Wait.
What's your name?
Elliot.
Thanks, Elliot.
Sorry I made you late.
Hope you can still
do your important thing.
Hey, Elliot?
Can I see you again?
Yeah.
Before you go, I'll take
you to see The Martian.
Ifs always better to see
movies on the big screen.
Really?
Yeah.
Thanks, Elliot.
I think you'll like it.
Matt Damon is awesome.
Stay here.
I've got something for you.
Because you said
you were sick.
Bye.
You again. What the fuck
do you want?
You're gonna have a funeral
for your brother.
A proper one.
Okay, dipshit.
We're not having a funeral
for that waste of space.
Your problem is
you never knew him.
If you did, you'd know
he's not capable of that.
Get the fuck off my property
before I call the cops.
I'll go. But before I do,
you should probably change
your corporate email password.
Using your street address, even if
it's an old one, isn't the smartest.
Don't feel special.
I hack everyone.
From the emails I found,
you and your law firm
swapped some shady memos that I don't
think the IRS would look too kindly on.
What do you think
you found?
If you don't want me
sending them out,
make sure your brother
gets a funeral.
A good one.
I want an invite.
I'll make sure
you get my email.
Bullshit.
Got these from Hard Andy.
One of your shady clients
I was talking about.
I won't be needing
them anymore.
The money you make
selling them back to him
will more than pay
for a funeral.
Start writing a eulogy.
A good one.
I'll be in the back
listening.
It's me.
Angela.
Come on. Open up.
Let's talk.
I'm worried about you.
I wish I could say something
that could snap you out of this.
Remember when we used to do
our wishing game?
We'd close our eyes,
and we'd wish for something.
Whatever we wanted.
We both wished we could
get bigger bedrooms.
That was a big one.
You would always wish
for more protractors,
which was weird.
I would wish
for a faster computer.
Probably faster modem too.
You would wish
for better clothes.
I didn't really care
about that.
We both...
we both wished
we could drive.
I just wanted to drive away.
We wanted to go
on road trips.
And eat lots
of Sour Patch Kids
that we would buy
from gas stations.
After we made
all our wishes...
We'd close our eyes
really hard,
hoping that when
we opened them,
it'd all come true.
And we thought the harder
we closed them,
the stronger our wishes
would be.
And even though
they never came true,
we still liked doing it.
Because the ending was never
our favorite part, anyway.
It was the wishing.
I didn't get that at first.
You remember
what you used to say to me
right before we opened
our eyes...
that would make it all better?
No matter what happens,
we'll be okay.
That's the thing
about deletion.
It's not always permanent.
There are many reasons why you wanna
recover a file you just deleted.
When you have that
moment of panic,
where it hits you,
where that thing you thought
had no value suddenly
becomes important.
Where you suddenly find
new purpose for it.
Maybe there are still things
left for me to do.