Everywhere I look
you're there.
That is why
I wanted to meet.
So I could find out
why you are so special
to Phillip Price.
Why come after me?
Your pet project
Angela Moss was allowed
to continue
with her lawsuit
which put my plans
in jeopardy.
We're not safe here.
I have to warn her.
She has to know
what they heard.
Ms. Moss. Ms. Moss, I'm gonna
need you to come with us.
We're ready.
My exploit
will give me full access
to their management
interface.
Now I own the Dark Army.
I suppose there's
some banal excuse
why a month
isn't enough time
to get my project shipped
to the Congo?
Trenton's right. Encryption keys
were exported the night of the hack.
Why would Romero do this?
He did it for the
reason we need those keys now,
in case our revolution failed.
Bang!
I don't trust him. ELLIOT:
AH of his state's
in the FBI evidence
storage system.
The FBI. The Dark Army
has a man on the inside.
I'll hit up my contact.
We can't trust them.
I might have an angle.
DiPIERRO: She was in my home
attempting to steal my badge
to get on Sentinel.
There are files that can help
decrypt all of E Cam's data.
What's the plan here?
She talks like
she knows everything.
How do you want to proceed?
We haven't seen
each other in months.
We've been battling each other
in our own voids.
When we were kids, Darlene
and I, we made this snowman.
That was the day my dad
pushed me out the window.
You remember when we made
Kevin McCallister?
Do you want to talk about it'?
Do you remember
when you said
Elliot would one day follow
in the footsteps
of his father?
I think it's time
he died for us, too.
Darlene's not
responding to any of my texts.
If Dark Army's targeting me,
then they're gonna
target her next.
Hopefully, she made it
to our rendezvous.
Wake up.
Let's go.
You're coming with me.
Finally you guys came
to your sen...
Dude, what the fuck?
Shut up.
Are you seriously gonna
arrest me right now?
I told you we can
fix this, okay?
Let's just log into Sentinel.
I said shut the fuck up.
Ifs the EC and 302 from
last night, the Alderson case.
I just submitted it
for upload.
Why are you giving me this'?
Uh, sorry, Santiago
must not have told you.
You're on the Alderson arrest.
I brought her in last night.
No clue what
you're talking about.
I'm headed to JFK in 20.
Got a flight
to San Fran today.
Santiago!
What are you doing?
Taking her to holding.
I thought you were putting
Agent Kaz on this.
Why are you
doing this yourself'?
The ADIC wanted
her in holding.
That's what I'm doing.
Get back inside.
Fine, I'll take it up
with the ADIC then.
Are you gonna finally tell me
what the fuck is going on?
I can't talk to you
about it, Dom.
You're not authorized to know.
There's intel you're not privy
to that's connected to this.
I'd be more comfortable if
we took it up with the ADIC.
If you want to call him,
you can.
But I...
I just don't want you
to embarrass yourself.
What?
Are you scared of me now?
There are cameras everywhere.
You really think
I'm going to do...
She's not here.
Mr. Robot's note.
If what he said is true and
the Dark Army owns the FBI,
then maybe she ran into them
while she was trying
to access Sentinel.
Shit.
Dark Army has dozens
of operatives
who live in and around
Manhattan.
Combing through their command
and control server
is going to take too long.
There are over 600,000
compromised systems on here.
I can't go through every one.
I don't even know
what I'm searching for.
I need something to go on.
A name, place,
something, anything.
Think, think, think.
What do I know?
Anything you can remember?
Any detail?
Anything. Tell me something.
Don't you get it?
She's gonna die.
Darlene's gonna die.
She's gonna fucking die
like everyone else.
I should have never done this.
I should have left this alone.
I'll never learn.
I brought this on myself.
This is on me.
For how many'?
One.
So, Ferris wheel.
Cute touch.
I need information from you.
You do not get to summon me
like you're Ali Babe,
squeeze me for information then
shove me back in some lamp.
Darlene's in trouble!
She might already be dead.
The whole reason you're
in this goddamn mess
is because we're
not working together,
because you refuse
to talk to me.
I wish that were true.
The sick part is...
I actually missed you.
The only reason
we haven't been talking...
ls because I haven't
let myself.
'Cause I've been
scared of you.
The part of... me that is you.
Why are we talking now'?
The 71 buildings.
I didn't know about that.
If you did,
would you have done it'?
Would you have done it?
I would have...
I would have found
another way.
Because as much as there
is a part of you in me...
There is a part of me in you.
Your note on the mirror,
what did you mean by it?
What do you know?
I need to find Darlene.
Tell me what you know.
The FBI...
has a mole.
You piece of shit.
The attack in China.
While you were hiding
in your room,
knowing the rest of us
were getting blown to pieces.
Cisco.
You helped them get to him
before we did, didn't you?
And the Tyrell cover-up.
You helped frame...
Markesh and Biswas.
This whole time, we've been
punching ourselves in the face
because of you!
All I know is, if you were
put in my position...
Nothing would make me betray
everything I stand for.
You know one thing I'll say
about you, DiPierro,
your naivete is adorable.
It's easy for you to play
a hero in the backseat,
but that's all world's ever
amounted to.
The backseat.
The things I did.
I mean, the... The things
that I have to do...
Are you seriously trying
to paint yourself a saint now
after what you've put us
through?
You know, the only reason
your girlfriend here is alive
is because I never told the
Dark Army she was a CHS.
Believe or not,
I'm not a bad guy, DiPierro.
You don't understand
what they put me through.
What they hold over me,
but you will.
Soon enough.
There's
the cocksucker.
Dead center.
According to Wellick,
he's been working both sides
the whole time.
Probably the reason we didn't
get pegged for Five/Nine.
We gotta find a way
to trace him.
Why don't we jump
on his desktop?
I already did that remotely,
nothing useful.
Which means whatever
we're looking for is physical.
Number sets.
It's another cipher code.
Not this shit again.
This has gotta give us
a location.
Elliot.
Just give me a minute.
Just finished this book.
I got it on tape.
Didn't care much
for the ending.
I mean, a story can have
a mediocre beginning
and middle,
and oftentimes it does,
but always got to have
a wow ending.
Otherwise, what's the point?
Shit.
If he's here that means
they must have Darlene.
Maybe I can manipulate him
into helping us.
Quick.
What do we know about...
Whatever scheme
you're trying to come up
with right now
It ain't gonna change
the inevitable, so...
I strongly recommend
you choose the easy way here
and come with me.
How'd you sleep last night?
I didn't.
I've been waiting all night.
I need to see her
as soon as possible.
I have important information
for her.
It's a beautiful day,
don't you think'?
LOOK.
There are people
that are trying to stop her.
I need to tell her.
Oh, I'm just
the house manager.
But you can discuss that with
Mr. Price when he arrives.
I thought we'd get some
breakfast first.
Do you like pancakes?
It's this way.
Elliot.
Don't fucking move.
We are walking into some
fucking hillbilly shit here.
Now, look.
I know this is all fucked up,
but it's salvageable.
There's a lot of clean-up
at the FBI
you're going to have
to take care of for me.
Mmm-hmm.
So this is the plus-one
you've been squawking about?
You're not turning this
around on me.
Not after the fucking day
I've had,
cleaning up your mess
once again.
I'm over it.
You hear me?
It's high time you guys start
cleaning up my mess
for a change.
Uh-huh.
And by "mess" I assume
you mean her.
I know how to fix this.
So do I.
All right.
Come on, Miss, let's go.
Leon, you got this?
Yeah, I got it.
Are you okay?
Is that a joke?
We're in a fucking barn out
in the middle of nowhere
with a handful
of psychos.
"No" is the answer.
DiPIERRO: Listen, sir.
I don't know what you
think I did, but...
This guy's a liability to you.
He's gotten sloppy.
You don't have to do this.
Dom.
My bosses know
about everything.
There's security camera
footage of him kidnapping
Ms. Alderson and me...
Miss.
Stop talking, huh'?
Okay, we got two operatives.
Leon's pretty good
with a knife.
What are you thinking?
I'm not trying to escape.
Elliot, these guys aren't
fucking around.
Who do you think you're going
to talk to out here?
Who do you think?
White rose.
You've played
that game already.
She doesn't want to see you.
She's seeing us right now.
Fuck me.
Now wait a minute.
Let's just slow things
down a bit.
We can flip her.
She can be very valuable.
No way I'm flipping.
Dom.
Don't be stupid.
Listen to me.
I'm trying to get you out
of this alive.
Valuable, huh?
You think she would've gone
far in the Bureau?
She would have been one
of the youngest ASACs ever,
still could be.
No, she's a rising star.
Gumption.
But it's like she said,
no way she's flipping.
Hey.
Oh, no, no, don't get
too worked up, Miss.
Just look at the sky.
Take a deep breath.
Try to enjoy the fresh air.
Wait, wait, wait. Dom.
Just tell him you'll flip.
This isn't worth it.
You can...
Oh, don't mind that.
We're retiring
this shit-stain.
And you're taking his place.
You work for
the Dark Army now.
You're gonna go back
to the FBI.
It's gonna be business
as usual.
You're gonna feed us
any information
and answer all our requests.
Fuck you.
Now, Dom.
You're gonna need to get your head
around the position you're in here.
I'm no traitor.
You should kill me now
because the first thing I do
when you let me go is arrest
your fucking ass.
The name of your youngest
family member,
what is it?
Oh, that's right.
Four-year-old Jamie DiPierro
of Morrisville.
That's your brother
Joseph's kid, right'?
Yeah.
I want you to look
at this jerk-off
and imagine it's little Jamie.
Now I want you to imagine
your morn Trudie,
in Philly.
Now imagine Uncle Chris
one morning
as he's picking up his copy
of the Dallas Morning Star!
Or you're older brother,
Jerry,
while he's watching
Wheel... of... Fortune!
Am I illustrating my point'?
Dom, I'm going
to need verbal confirmation
that you're grasping the
details of this agreement!
Okay.
In time,
this will get easier
to live with.
I promise.
Head into the barn
and await further instructions
on how to clear up
Santiago's missteps.
Now, forgive me
while I take a moment
to center myself.
This next bunch...
These are for me.
Jesus, Dom, what happened?
Looks like she's just got
her initiation.
Want some of
this catnip, girl'?
All right.
Suit yourself.
All right, if we don't figure
out a way to get out of here,
they are going to kill us.
Look around you.
They've been instructed
to wait.
Not act.
Wait for what?
They're preparing for someone
important to come.
I took care of everything.
As instructed.
Everyone's loaded up
in the barn.
You might want
to send your guys
to the woodpile over there.
I had to kill the FBI mole.
That's the bad news.
Good news, I got you
someone even better.
She doesn't have
as high of a rank,
but she's got
tremendous upside.
Besides...
That guy was a dickhead.
Anyway.
She's in the barn as well.
Where are you going?
Me, I'm gonna take
that overdue sabbatical
I keep talking about.
Finally get to finish my book.
Well, that's the goal anyway.
I'm thinking the Sandals
in Barbados.
They got a good special
running this month.
You are
not going anywhere.
We have work to do.
Tell me something.
She still making
her spontaneous overtures?
She make you taste her yet?
Remember, doll face,
I was you years ago.
And I've already done my time.
I think she'll be good
with me.
Glad we did this.
I want to leave.
My staff not keeping
you comfortable?
I wouldn't have come
if I had known
this was your house.
I was getting concerned
about you.
Hadn't been to work for weeks,
you're not answering
your phone, your emails.
I sent someone
to your apartment.
When I saw what you
were doing, I felt I...
I had to intervene.
I'm not
supposed to be here.
And where do you think
you're supposed to be?
You know where.
With her.
She has a plan.
Yes, I've known about
her delusional plan for years.
You don't know anything.
Mr. Alderson.
I had a chance to review
your paperwork for Stage 3.
Surprisingly...
It's bullshit.
There is no Stage 3,
but you already knew that.
I'm glad we can be honest.
Now we can talk.
The only reason
you're involved in any of this
is because I had Colby
hire you.
I needed to manipulate you
into dropping
that contingency
from your lawsuit.
You were threatening
her plant.
And she would have
done anything
to stop those inspections,
including killing you.
Why would you care
if she killed me?
You don't care about anyone
but yourself.
Let go of them.
Then we can talk.
But if I didn't have her
then how am I going
to keep you honest?
I own everything.
I own every single system
the Dark Army has compromised.
I met your mother.
Emily.
Thirty two years ago.
When you took my laptop,
you infected yourself
with my malware.
If you hurt her,
it will all get released.
Every bribe, blackmail,
extortion, operation,
all your illegal connections,
everything will go public.
The entire Dark Army history.
That's impossible.
And here I thought
we were going to be honest.
We were both
working at E Corp.
We dated for quite some time.
Seven days ago,
the Russian government
hired you to hack
the DNC.
Elliot.
Two days before that,
you bribed the president of
South Korea to allow backdoors
in all
of their military networks.
You're just pissing him off.
Three weeks before that,
you used Phillip Price
to annex the Congo for China.
Am I being more honest now?
I loved her.
Deep?!'-
But I never told her.
If one of us dies,
everything gets leaked.
Well, we can survive a leak.
You can't survive a bullet
through your throat.
The closer we became,
the more I held back.
I was cruel to her
in that way.
It made me feel strong...
To torture her like that...
like that.
We have an opportunity
for both of us
to leave with what we want.
I know exactly what you want.
You want to reverse Five! Nine.
And honestly we couldn't
careless about that.
Ifs already served
its purpose.
When she told me
she was pregnant,
she was very emphatic
that her child
wasn't going to
be raised by a monster,
as she put it.
No!
I also know how to move
whatever project you have
in the Washington
Township Plant to the Congo.
While you sit back,
missing your deadlines,
doing nothing,
I've engineered a hack that
can solve all of your problems
and I'm willing
to give it to you.
Do you hear me?
I can move your projects
to the Congo!
You'll get what you want!
We won't bother you anymore!
Sometime after that
she met and then...
She married your father.
Who agreed to raise you
as his own.
You're very
sure of yourself.
You are just one hacker.
What makes you believe
that you are better
than an army of people
exactly like you?
Because I am.
I did something in one night
you've been trying to pull off
for months.
I never planned
on telling you,
until I realized what
Whiterose had done to you.
Look, it's not possible
what she's talking about.
Angela, this so-called project
of hers,
it stems from an obsessive,
psychotic denial of reality.
Don't do this.
Let me help you.
I'm sorry, Mr. Alderson.
You're good at playing games.
But this was simply
the wrong hand to play.
She has murdered
countless people
lo fulfill this... this
ridiculous fantasy.
History...
is finally coming for you.
What is this?
I don't believe you.
You're lying.
I am your father.
Biologically speaking, anyway.
I think that's you, brah.
The Cyber Bombings...
All of those people.
That was my fault.
She used me for that.
Your jealousy has always
blinded you
to Mr. Alderson's value.
That is why you can never see
my plan through to the end.
I have to believe
there was a purpose.
Pettiness.
It was a dig at me.
It's that small,
unfortunately.
You can't believe him.
He's... He's lying.
Know that
I will find you
as soon as our project
is complete.
But for the here and now...
our time has come...
lo an end.
No, it's not over.
It's not over.
It can't be.
She was gonna bring
my mom back.
We were gonna be reunited.
You made an offer, cuz.
Now it's time to pay up.
Please tell me
you're not bluffing.
What are you gonna
do to her?
What are you asking?
Retribution.
I want ii.
Coast Guard is allowing
the shipment
of humanitarian aid to Iran.
Trust me.
It'll work.
I'm afraid your
only move here...
Accept that
you've been conned.
It's downloaded.
Now, you know
I ain't got to tell you
what they going to do
if this don't check out right.
It'll checkout.
You know I've always had
faith in you, cuz.
Do your thing.
Find a way to live
with what you did.
What do we do now?
Undo the hack.
Don't think
I'm doing this for you.
Dom.
You are a terrible person.
Don't ever convince
yourself of anything else.
All you deserve
for the rest of your life...
is pure and utter agony.
That'll begin to scratch
the surface
of how I feel about you.
You've taken everything
from me.
My whole life...
is ruined because of you.
Live with that.
Die with that.
The FBI had Romero's
keylogger files,
but he encrypted them
with a password.
Thing is, the FBI
didn't know Romero.
I do.
Is this really it?
The moment this can
all truly end?
Reverse everything we've done.
Finally bring Five/Nine
to an end.
This is it.
Everything that was typed
on those machines
at the arcade
on the night of the hack.
So what'd you find?
He didn't do it.
Romero was just spying on us.
He caught someone else
exporting the key data.
If he didn't do it,
then who the fuck did?
Reminder,
today's city-wide curfew
starts at 9:00 p.m.
this evening
until 4:00 a.m.
tomorrow morning.
Stay indoors
and stay off the streets.
Why did you bring up
Kevin McCallister?
The snowman.
When we were in Coney Island,
you asked me if I remembered.
What was that all about?
It felt so random.
That was the day Dad
pushed me out the window.
What are you...
what do you mean...
Dad pushed you out the window?
He was mad that I told Mom
about his cancer,
and he pushed me
out the window.
You were young.
I guess I never told you.
What are you talking
about Elliot?
I was there.
We were in your room
looking for a camera
when Dad came home.
For some reason
you freaked out and told me
to go hide in the closet.
Then Dad came in the room,
and all of the sudden
you... I don't know.
You just snapped.
You started swinging
your baseball bat,
hitting everything.
No.
That's not what happened.
Trust me, I remember.
You took your baseball bat
and you smashed the window,
and then you kept telling Dad
you were gonna jump.
Elliot, you weren't pushed.
You jumped.
I don't remember
any of that.
Well, I'm here to remember
for you.
This is our stop.
I'm gonna ride the train
a little longer.
Are you okay?
I'll get it done.
Hey. The email from Trenton.
I know she sent it to you
because she could trust you.
The same as I always have.
I'm gonna get off
at the next stop.
I think you
should come with me.
It wasn't Romero.
It was you who exported
the keys.
Why'?
We're close, Elliot.
You pull the ripcord now
and everything will be
for nothing.
There was a huge cost
to get to this point.
I still believe if we hold out
a little longer...
No.
You do this,
and they will have won.
You really believe undoing
this is going to fix anything?
Huh? Do you?
I mean, who is this
really gonna help?
Me.
I'm doing this for me.
I can't live with
what I did anymore.
And you're wrong.
They won't win.
Because one good thing
came out of all of this.
They showed themselves,
the top 1% of the 1%,
the ones in control,
the ones who play God
without permission.
And now I'm gonna take
them down.
All of them.
Whatever happens after this,
I want us to keep talking.
I want us to be a team.
I know I can't force you so...
I'm asking.
'Jumped.
I wasn't pushed.
Did you know that'?
You asked me before
why I did this.
We, the damned!
The reason is
I thought...
What if we were wrong?
What if there's something
we weren't seeing?
What if we failed?
The real
reason is it's...
It's because it's what you
would've done.
You were right.
There was a pan' of you in me.
I never wanted
to tell you that
because it's not in my nature.
It's not why I exist.
Only you know why I'm here.
On the night of the hack,
I transferred the keys
from the arcade...
to a remote virtual machine
on our box at home.
I then burned it to a CD.
You'll find the seed data
and the algorithm
embedded in one
of those pictures.
You'll know the one.
With those two pieces, you
should be able to regenerate
the keys that were used
to encrypt all
of E Corp's data.
And with that...
You can make it like
Five/Nine never happened.
This is a reminder,
today's city-wide curfew
begins at 9:00 p.m.
this evening
through 4:00 a.m.
tomorrow morning.
Stay indoors
and off the streets.
Dude, what the fuck?
Slow down.
Fucking asshole.
Shit.
Like I was saying, this shit
has been fucking rough.
I hear you.
It's hit everybody.
Yeah, the difference being
when it hits you,
you don't have to suck
some cuck's shrimp dick
to buy a damn sandwich.
This is true.
I think things are gonna
change though.
For the better.
Soon, so...
Hang in there.
Hanging's what I do best.
But I don't know
what you mean.
E Corp's in
a world of shit.
Daddy lost both his homes
and his bike 'cause of them.
And now this country's
attackin' Iran.
If anything, this is the calm
before the damn storm.
Yeah, well...
Hold out hope.
Trust me.
I think...
I think E Corp will be able
to bring back their lost data.
Yeah, well,
I hope not.
That just means debt's
gonna come back.
And I certainly don't know
how my $80,000 student loan
I owe Parsons is gonna
help me fix anything.
Well, it's a start.
Path to recovery.
The economy will start
to bounce hack.
Girl, you don't
have to sound so simplistic.
That's not the way this
crony capitalism shit works.
Shit, educate yourself
on some Marx
before you go just theorizing
about economic forces.
Okay, so...
What do you think
would fix all of this then?
An act of God.
And right about now,
he needs a hell
of a good blow job, just like
every other stressed-out,
powerful motherfucker
trying to hold their shit
together, right?
Well, this is me.
I'm really glad
I met you tonight.
Me too, babes.
Why you coming to this
ugly ass building anyways?
My brother lives here.
You think he'd be down
for a good time tonight?
Well, he definitely needs
to get laid, but...
I don't think
that's gonna happen.
Shit.
What?
There go them
damn eses again.
Fuck, and now they parking.
LOOK.
I got to go, babe.
Can I help you, fellas?
My sister,
only the north stars
of the cosmos
can help a visionary like me.
But, yes,
you can shine alight
on a dark corner of my mind.
What?
Who are you'?
I'm just...
I'm just a brave traveler
who's finally come home.