Stay right there!
Don't you fucking move!
Why'd he surrender?
Who is your leader?
Fsociety.
A honeypot?
For what?
A specific server, involved in
the last fsociety attack. CS30.
You should know that nothings
gonna come from this.
It's nice to
finally meet you.
Are you sure
he is good to go?
When we spoke earlier,
he was looking at me
like we'd never met.
Make sure
this doesn't happen again.
Fucking weirdo.
I texted
you the address.
Is that where Tyrell is?
Yes.
DiPIERRO: We gotta act before Wellick
disappears for another five months.
You said you'd bring
my family to me.
It's gonna work out
the way we discussed.
Angela, whatever
Whiterose told you is a lie.
These consequences
were necessary...
People are going to die!
No, they're going to be fine!
Listen to me.
You have to stop the attack.
There's one last thing
I need in order to execute,
the full force
of the Dark Army.
A reported 71 buildings
owned by E Corp
exploded or caught fire.
When you see Whiterose, make
sure you say I did you good.
We're gonna stay
with my buddy in Arizona.
If what I discovered is real,
do you know what that means'?
We can potentially undo
this whole thing.
Excuse me,
do you have the time?
REPORTER ON TV; Reports are still
coming in from across the country...
But based on
the number of targets,
we are now in the midst of the
worst attack on U. S. soil
in the history of our nation.
In a series of seemingly orchestrated
strikes across the country,
a reported 71 buildings
owned by E Corp
exploded or caught fire.
There has been
no official confirmation,
or even speculation,
as to what caused
the explosions
and fires to occur.
Officials with knowledge
of the attacks
have stated
that the death toll...
I know it may seem petty
in light of today, but...
I just can't stop
thinking about it.
Keep turning it over
in my mind.
Frasier.
Now, my homie said
it's iconic and shit.
Even won a record 37
Primetime Emmys, or whatever.
So I started watching.
And I'm cool with suspending
my disbelief a little,
but this?
Am I really supposed
to believe
a baldin' white dude
from Seattle
gets to smash that much?
And it's not like he was
slaying hood rats, neither.
This nigga get more butt
than ashtrays.
Turned me off from the fucking
situation comedies altogether.
Had to cleanse the palate.
And I know it only got
one Emmy nomination,
but I'll tell you,
you wanna see
a believable protagonist
doing extraordinary shit?
Don't sleep
on Knight Rider, yo.
As of now, no one
has claimed responsibility
for this nightmarish attack.
You don't have to kill us.
You know, we can... We...
We can work with you.
Haven't... Haven't
enough people died already today?
My man.
My man...
Relax.
Calm down.
If I was here to take you out,
would've done it already.
Your roomie here serves
as a prime example to that.
Then what is it?
Why are you here?
Oh, just to babysit,
to keep you guys
safe and sound.
will be tested
in the coming days
as we learn more, as we find
those responsible...
You know,
it's kinda sad, actually,
the general lack of respect
afforded to Knight Rider.
They throw fucking gold
statues at the Crane brothers,
but Michael Knight and KITT,
their relationship predicted
the current societal
dependence on technology,
and that was 30 years ago.
Plus, anytime Mike spits game
on a chick,
I swear, I believe
every goddamn word.
If nothing else,
Knight Rider should've won
a fucking statue
for his dope ass theme song.
I mean, the shit
just stays with you.
Stuck in my head
right now, in fact.
A National Terrorism
Advisory System
has issued an imminent
alert bulletin,
after a reported
71 E Corp buildings
were targeted
in a coordinated attack
unlike any the world has seen.
At this time,
many looming questions remain.
The cause of the explosions that
brought so much destruction,
or worse, if any additional attacks
are to follow.
Unfortunately, what we do know
is that...
Elliot, it's okay.
Just calm down
and keep breathing.
Okay.
And you can tell me
what it is
that you think you did, okay'?
Just breathe,
and whenever you're ready,
we can talk.
Okay.
Uh...
I-n-
I think we...
I'm... I'm sorry.
I don't know if I can say it.
I don't know if I can say it,
what... I'm sorry, Krista.
What... What he...
Or I...
What... What...
What we both may have done,
I don't know if I can say it.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry,
I don't know if I can say it.
I can't. I'm sorry.
Nice to see you again,
beautiful.
Hello, Mr. Robot.
Of course he comes running
to you after today.
So predictable.
Elliot said he wanted
to speak to me, but
conscious or not, I suspect that
he thought it was more important
that I speak to you.
Why do you have to keep
going through a middleman?
Why can't he just
speak to me himself?
I'm not sure he wants to,
but I wanna help you
figure out why.
Elliot told me he's worried
that you may have done
something harmful.
Do you know what
he might be referencing?
Everything that happened today
is because he was ignoring
our responsibilities.
What happened exactly?
The point is...
It's not me
he has to worry about.
Ifs the others,
the real string pullers.
Who would that be?
You wanna know
what's really going on'?
Look around, sweetheart.
I'm not the only one
under their thumb.
They're manipulating
everything, always,
just 10 line their own pockets,
to have total control.
But that's the conspiracy,
man.
So you and Elliot...
you want to challenge
these manipulators?
Me and Elliot wanted
to take the control away,
give it back to the ones
who were getting shit on.
We got halfway there,
until someone swiped my ideas
and warped them to suit
whatever bullshit agenda
served their self-interest.
That's what Five/Nine
was about,
our revolution.
So you are a supporter
of Five/Nine?
Supporter?
I was no supporter.
I was the architect!
How about telling me
why you think
Elliot might be upset
with you?
I don't have time
for this shit.
I gotta find the pricks
who screwed me.
Turn on the news, lady.
All these buildings
fucking blowing up.
I think they're trying
to pin that shit on me.
I know it.
It ain't happening.
So, the attacks today were a
part of the revolution you created?
Is that what you're saying?
We were only supposed
to take out one location,
once all the paper records
were centralized.
That was it.
Yeah, I've gotta be
honest with you, Mr. Robot,
this sounds like
delusions of grandeur.
How else do you explain what
the authorities are saying?
They claim to have
the man responsible.
Wellick?
No, he was working for me,
but you and the rest
of the world
are never gonna know that,
because you keep happily
lapping up those sugar-coated
pearls of semen
they keep pouring down
your throats.
You're buying the narrative
that they've been pushing
for months.
Pigs at a trough!
You still don't believe me.
You're indulging me right now,
like I'm one
of your nutso patients.
Do the math.
Elliot worked at Allsafe,
ground zero for Five/Nine.
He was also arrested
for hacking.
He even hacked you,
didn't he?
And he's completely
out of his mind.
You add all that up...
You still want to doubt me?
Good people of Earth,
there is more up our sleeves.
Seventy-one buildings
is a parlor trick.
Our true act of sorcery
will astound
within the next 24 hours.
To all fat cats,
gluttons, and honchos,
as you lazily don
your ribbons of remembrance
for this tragic day,
do not forget,
the clock is ticking.
I think the public
may lose faith in the Bureau,
once they learn
that you squandered
the chance to prevent
another attack.
I'm not gonna be strong-armed,
not by you,
not after today.
Then I suggest
you start taking
my client's words seriously.
DiPIERRO: This is unreal.
The country's under attack,
and you're protecting him?
Wellick was targeted,
because of his access
and credentials at E Corp.
These terrorists threatened
his wife and son
if he didn't comply.
For five straight months,
my client was held captive
in a basement.
You can't expect us
to buy this.
We have confirmation.
Wellick gave
an unauthorized order
to put server CS30
back on the network,
the same night
the hack was initiated,
all while being
investigated for murder.
Yeah, a charge
for which he's been cleared.
DiPIERRO: That doesn't change
the facts.
Wellick got passed over
for CTO,
got fired, two days later,
disappears,
and now, hours before
the largest terror attack ever
on U.S. soil, Wellick resurfaces,
claiming he was kidnapped.
So, what,
are you charging my client
with coincidental resurfacing?
We don't call that coincidence
around here.
We call it bullshit. Dom...
We have motive.
Yeah, with no hard evidence.
But here's what you do have.
You have a guy
that'll point you
to the terrorists
who held him hostage,
the actual people
behind the attacks,
the same ones planning
more destruction.
Mr. Wellick can ID them,
and tell you
their likely location,
in exchange for protection
and immunity.
We're not gonna cut a deal.
We're gonna charge him and just add
obstruction of justice on top of it.
You saw the video.
Time is not a luxury
that you have,
not with another attack
on the horizon, so...
do you really wanna sit here
and continue to quibble
about Mr. Wellick?
DiPIERRO: Let's just
round them all up,
Darlene, Elliot, Angela Moss.
Let's just haul 'em all
in here and go at 'em hard.
Wellick's lawyer
is right.
Time is not
our friend here.
And if Tyrell can get us
two workable leads...
We're being played!
How do you not see this?
I still think
the Dark Army's involved,
and bringing in the others
might expose that.
I have to brief Carney,
and he has to brief
the President.
I won't go to them with
half-assed theories again,
not when this much
is on the line.
Why do you keep ignoring
our credible sources?
The most credible one
being in that room.
Tyrell Wellick's
name alone
is going to play better
with them than the others.
Play better?
Are you already wondering
how this is gonna look?
You wanna cover this up
to the FBI Director
and the President
of the United States?
Spare me
the conspiracy theories.
I need to bring them
something concrete.
And if Wellick's lying?
Then this deal is off,
and we have our guy.
It's a win-win for us,
either way.
Why are you fighting
with me on this?
Because somethings
not adding up.
What's that
supposed to mean'?
I don't know if this is
because you're overworked
or stressed out
or just under some delusion
that you're a fucking
super-cop, but it stops now.
You report to me.
Start remembering that.
As to what caused
the explosions and fires to...
Tyrell Wellick
and took him into custody...
Warned of another attack
within the next 24 hours.
Of our company's
paper rec...
Officials with
knowledge of the attacks
have stated
that the death toll
is expected to be well...
Right now,
the estimate's around 3,000.
What estimate?
The dead.
But it's still climbing.
Okay, maybe you should just
chill with the TV for a second.
They're gonna be okay, right?
Who's that?
All those people who died.
Do you think
that they're gonna be okay'?
I'm gonna go grab my shit
and come back.
It won't be long.
Just don't go anywhere, okay?
Can we just take a break?
I, I might need a minute.
Unfortunately,
that's not possible.
As you know,
this is time-sensitive.
Okay.
But after this,
I get to see my family, yes'?
It's very important
that I see my wife and child.
I'll be sure to relay
your request to my superior.
For now, though,
need your eyes on that book.
You shouldn't have
told anyone, Mom.
I could get in trouble
for telling you.
Well, you can't be afraid
to leave the house.
You still have
two treatments left.
Don't listen to that video.
It's just a scare tactic.
We caught the guy.
Fine, fine...
I'll call Dr. Zeigler,
and ask if it can wait.
I love you too.
REPORTER; The operation took place
at Red Wheelbarrow Barbecue,
it's a popular
fast food restaurant
in Manhattan's Flatiron
District.
Wellick ID'd
the two suspects,
both corroborated
by Sasan Nouri,
our fsociety video perp.
You call it in?
We're about to release
a BOLO.
Nice work, Stanchek.
I'll see you down
in the squad room.
Okay.
And, sir?
What?
It's Wellick.
He keeps asking
about his family.
He wants to see 'em.
It's just us now.
We can speak freely.
You need to get anything
off your chest?
Well,
there's some information
that's about to be declassified
for public release,
and before you hear it
from your lawyer
or somebody else,
I wanted to personally come
here and deliver it to you.
Rumor has it you're asking
about your family?
Yes, I've been told,
if I cooperate...
Your wife's dead.
Almost two weeks now.
What?
No, you must be mistaken.
Lovers' quarrel
with a dude she was banging.
He shot her in the head
at close range.
It's nasty stuff.
Lies. You're lying.
Which means that your son
is currently being raised
at Peaceful Acres Foster Care.
Now, last I checked, it was
only a one in five abuse rate.
Decent odds.
No.
This can't be true.
I know you're lying.
I want to see my wife.
I demand it.
If you're thinking about
telling anyone here about me,
if you veer
from the plan at all,
I promise, you won't live
to place a flower
at your wife's grave.
And your son...
I'll make it
my personal mission
to ensure he becomes
a statistic.
Just another forgotten child,
lost to the system, forever.
I know what this is. You
sent that email to the FBI.
I knew the Dark Army
would find out.
I'm not stupid.
I never sent the email.
How do you explain this?
Why are we here?
Kay, maybe he's not gonna
kill us, but someone sure is.
If anything
does happen to us,
if I don't make it
back to my computer,
I sent the email to go out
automatically
to someone I trust.
I'm supposed to be
on a J-Date with Juanita
at Ruby Tuesdays, as we speak.
She's probably
worried about me.
Hey. Hey, maybe...
Maybe she'll call the cops,
report me missing.
Doubt it.
Besides, what are you even
doing on J-Date?
You're not even Jewish.
And doesn't sound
like she is, either.
I told you, my 23andMe said
I'm 6% Ashkenazi,
and for your information,
her full name is
Juanita Rosenberg.
Look, do you think I wanna be
stuck in the backseat
of a psychopath's Cadillac
with you?
I should be at home
with my family.
My brother is probably
flipping out right now.
You think your brother's
flipping out?
That guy
slit my friend's throat,
and now he's digging
what could be a mass grave
over there.
Yeah. If your brother's
flipping out,
I'm like a Sam Kinison
stand-up bit,
okay, Shelley Duvall
at the Overlook Hotel.
I'm at "hot mic'd
Christian Bale"
levels of intensity
and hysteria,
so please, don't talk to me
about flipping out.
Yes. Yes.
What... Hang on,
what are you doing'?
You gotta get us out of here.
I can't...
I don't know how to drive.
You have a genius level IQ,
and you can't work
an automatic transmission?
I grew up in the city.
I never had to learn.
Oh, yeah, well,
you do now, kay?
Get up there,
put pedal to the metal.
Yeah, okay, okay. Okay.
Floor it. Floor it.
Okay.
Floor it!
Floor m
Go, go, go, go, go!
Easy! Easy!
Damn.
That's no way
to treat a Caddie.
I can't just do nothing.
I almost went straight
to the authorities.
Oh, well, let's thank our lucky
stars you opted to call me first.
I told you what he said.
How can I not report this?
As your counsel
and your friend,
I should remind you,
you are bound
by doctor-patient privilege,
so unless he's stated intent
to do something in the future,
you can't turn him in.
Per HIPPA, you'll lose
your license and practice.
No, there's something
about this. I can feel it.
I know him.
I actually think
he might've been involved.
You know how many
crazies are out there
claiming responsibility
for the attacks?
The... The FBI and the police
are inundated by phone calls
from people
just like your client.
Fuck.
Any Updates?
They think the total
will be over 4,000.
But the number doesn't
really matter now...
Even if there's more.
What do you mean
“even if there's more"?
No matter what happens now,
everything will be fine.
Angela,
if there are more attacks,
you have to tell me.
I don't know
anything about them.
What are you doing?
Here, let me show you.
Okay. Watch.
See?
They all came back.
They're all fine.
Here, I'll show you again.
Told you.
Everyone's okay again.
Everyone's gonna be okay.
Our FBI reporters
say that there was evidence
found at Red Wheelbarrow
that Tyrell Wellick
had been hiding out
in the restaurant's basement.
The FBI's investigating
the possibility
that the team of fsociety
members behind Five/Nine
were operating
out of the barbecue eatery.
Interestingly enough,
the basement Itself
does not appear on any plans
or blueprints
reported with the city,
so ii is possible
that Tyrell Wellick
and fsociety were operating
unbeknownst to the Red
Wheelbarrow Barbecue.
While unsuspecting employees
are not a risk
to unwitting customers, justified
the notorious hacker claim.
Hey.
Hey!
Stage 2 was my operation.
You assholes went rogue...
As everyone
in this room knows well,
nothing creates profit
quite like global conflict.
Bullshit.
Ah, Phillip.
Always a pleasure,
though I am surprised
to see you
with all you have
on your plate.
You know damn well
I'm marooned here.
Well, then
a little bit of good news
on an otherwise trying day.
My government did finally
get around to signing
that accord.
Ecoin is poised to become
the world standard.
After your latest outburst,
nothing could save my company.
My actions were never meant
to harm E Corp.
On the contrary,
good old-fashioned
American sympathy
will go a long way in boosting
an already surging Ecoin.
E Corp is the very definition
of too big to fail.
Trust me' it will survive.
But, I won't.
So...
Is that... Is that what
all this has been then?
No.
When... When you
surprised me with Five/Nine,
I understood your move.
A false flag operation,
a temporary global crisis
to help me pressure
the administration
into giving you
your damn Congo.
All went according to plan,
which leaves me struggling
to find the upside to this.
Why come after me?
Think back
on that fateful night.
We sat,
listening to a young woman
playing a lyre.
A lawsuit was brewing
against my plant.
You told me you would...
Handle that person
as we usually do.
And yet,
your pet project,
Angela Moss,
was allowed to continue
with her lawsuit,
which put my plans
in jeopardy.
Your job was simple.
Manipulate her, control her.
You couldn't,
so I had to.
You little piece of shit.
Do not forget,
I installed you as CEO
only to protect my plant.
You were meant to do what
your predecessor couldn't,
and look at what happened
to him.
And now, you will follow
every order that I give you,
including hiring
your own replacement.
Fuck you.
In the interim,
I trust that there will be
no interference,
with my plant being relocated
to the Congo.
This... This is funny.
That's... That's...
That's all this is.
This is... This is, uh...
This is a joke
with a bad punchline.
You will also be called upon
to handle
all logistical issues,
proper access for my staff,
shipment of all materials...
No! You give me
the real reason, motherfucker.
Coming at me now.
What in God's name
do you hope to gain?
The opportunity
to teach a lesson.
A lesson?
You sadistic fuck.
You got your U.N. vote,
you got your plant,
you got everything you wanted!
No. You don't get off
that easy,
not until
you explain it to me.
You had to destroy so much.
Why'?
Because, Phillip...
I had to ask you twice.
What if we're being
recruited?
Recruited into digging
our own grave?
Look at the dimensions.
This hole's only big enough
for your friend.
What if were being recruited
into the Dark Army?
They could've...
They could've just asked.
They're probably planning
a follow-up attack,
and they need to use us
for our skills.
You know I can
hear you, right?
Even from way back here.
Every word.
Come on, man.
At least tell us what the
Dark Army wants from us.
Tell us what's going on,
or we stop digging!
We're serious.
I kinda like you two.
You guys are funny,
in a George-Elaine kinda way.
Still wouldn't try me, though.
I got a job to do, and
you don't wanna know
where this knife been.
You feel me?
Get out of the car.
Hurry up. I'm running
out of time here.
See that up there?
What is this?
You know why those people are
enjoying themselves so much,
even though
thousands died today
in the biggest attack
in U.S. history?
That wasn't my fault. That
wasn't supposed to happen.
I wanna know
who made that call.
Was it Tyrell?
What about this other attack?
That was never
a part of my plan.
See, kid, that's been
your mistake the entire time,
thinking this whole thing's
about your silly little plan.
No, your revolution
was only allowed lo happen
'cause it was bought
and paid for
by people like them.
Face it,
no matter how hard you try,
that's always the end result.
What the hell?
You're going in?
Mistress of a senator
we got on the payroll.
Powdered her nose
with some bad shit,
died a couple hours ago. I'm just
here to make it scandal-free.
You see what I mean?
Literally nothing
can stop these shindigs,
not thousands dead
across the country,
not a lifeless mistress
in the guest bathroom.
I guess they got here
sooner than I thought.
Worm-catching motherfuckers,
you know?
What's going on?
Who are these people?
This is where we say
our good-byes.
What?
You're leaving us with them'?
As you know, I'm...
I'm only a chaperone here.
Well, what happens now
to us?
Well, that will be
up to him.
And I got my fingers crossed
he treats you guys all right.
Mr. Markesh,
Ms. Biswas,
please follow me
into the garage.
What is this?
Take a seat.
PRESS.
Now,
tell me what you see.
Location confirmed.
We're in position.
Repeat. Location confirmed.
Be safe out there, boys.
Keep your head on a swivel.
Alpha team approaching the door.
Taking position.
Stand by for breach.
Assault force
is on the white side,
ready for primary breach.
A threat analysis
for the FAA's next-gen
lP-based system.
Targeting IPs in Chicago,
Atlanta,
L.A.
Bravo team set.
Holding perimeter.
This is malware
that targets
air-traffic control systems
at major airports.
They're planning
another attack,
probably like today, except
this time,
they're crashing planes.
Copy, Bravo. Got Alpha
and Bravo teams in position.
But the exploits
already written.
What do you need us for?
Execute,
execute, execute!
Go. Let's go.
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
Alpha team is in.
Repeat Alpha team is in.
In the Dark Army,
we understand what it's like
to believe in something.
We're willing to die
for our cause,
without thinking twice,
because we know
we are all soldiers
of something much larger.
Please don't kill us.
Please don't do this.
Room's clear.
Bravo team, stand by.
Something else
we all believe in,
self-sacrifice,
because when you serve
a higher power,
no act is more honorable
than suicide.
There is no greater gift
one can offer the cause...
Than everything.
Secure garage, Alpha One.
We can do whatever you want.
Please.
Maybe you can use us.
Everything in this room,
from the plans
to crash the airplanes
to your very presence,
is only here to tell a story.
Sadly, we have
no use for your skills,
but you both do serve
a very important purpose.
No. Oh, no, no, no...
No...
No, no, no, don't give me
the gun! No, please don't!
No! Stop!
No, please don't!
Please don't!
No!
You don't have to do this.
You don't have to...
Let's go. Go!
We got a camera,
a few terminals...
We got a body.
We have a body here.
Body?
ALPHA 11 Oh, my God.
Two bodies.
Hold on.
Got a thermal.
Find a light source?
One male civilian DOA
on the ground with a handgun.
One female civilian DOA
with a second handgun.
Room is clear.
TOC, be advised,
both jackpots are down.
Send in medics.
Alpha team to TOC,
area's secure.
We think it might
be Iranian.
Alert case squad and ERT.
Got an Iranian flag.
Fsociety masks.
Paraphernalia.
Camcorder.
Like a makeshift studio.
It's over, DiPierro.
I know we would've preferred
to have gotten them alive,
but at least we prevented
another attack.
You're actually gonna
get away with this.