Tyrell Wellick.
It's gonna be
fun working with you.
I think you're beautiful
I want to take you home.
Detectives came by.
They want to speak with you.
They found a body on the roof.
And you both did know
the deceased, Sharon Knowles.
Our network was
compromised yesterday.
That server needs
to remain a honeypot.
We have specific orders by Tyrell
Wellick to keep the request as is.
There's a reason we met.
There's something between us.
I can see it.
You're not seeing
what's above you.
Tyrell Wellick's gone.
I wake up in his SUV, and the
world's about to fall apart.
We were there to
investigate the hack,
and then we were under fire.
What you want,
I want it, too.
Someone's trying to make
contact with me.
25th & 8th.
Stage 2, the femtocell,
the back door...
I want it shut down.
I don't want to shoot
you, but I will.
I've always told you we'd end
up working together, Elliot.
Remember the night
of the hack?
Remember what happened to you?
What is it?
It's happening-
It's almost as if...
somethings come alive.
Now wait
a minute, Elliot.
Please, we should
talk about this.
No!
Did you see
what just happened?
Wait, wait, wait!
Do you not understand
what just happened?
The only thing that
happened is the gun jammed.
It won't happen again.
No, no, no! This is proof.
Don't you understand?
This is proof.
Proof of what?
When you told me I couldn't
see what was above me,
only in front of me.
What the fuck
are you talking about?
We...
are Gods.
You really are
a lunatic.
You held that gun
point blank at me and fired,
and yet I'm standing
right here talking to you.
What are the chances?
I don't know.
But shit happens
all the time.
This wasn't chance.
This was an act of God.
And we have been
invited into His circle
to lead this revolution.
You haven't been
invited anywhere.
You forced yourself in.
There's more
to your plan than this.
You're smart enough
to know that this hack alone
isn't gonna kill Evil Corp.
Once they realize
they can't recover the data,
they'll figure out
a way to re-create it,
and that's where
you'll need me.
Don't you
see it yet'?
From the first
time we met,
I felt something
between us.
This is what I felt.
An uncanny
connection, a bond.
We are meant
to work together.
That's what this
has all been about.
Work together? You're a psychopath.
How do I even trust you?
Pull the trigger again.
I'll accept whatever
fate decides.
Pull it!
Okay, Looney Tunes.
You're right.
There is a second
stage to this.
After tonight,
I don't know what kind
of support I'll have.
I could use your help.
Thank you, Elliot.
I love...
Some things are
better left unsaid.
Subtext, you know?
Sit down.
Take this.
You might just be
the perfect kind of crazy
who can protect me.
- .
From me.
This his car?
Yes.
What time did they arrive?
Shortly after 9:00 p.m.
This your first time
seeing the Swede'?
This Tyrell Wellick'?
YES.
What about the rest
of their crew?
Nope. No sign
of them.
All right, well...
Let's go.
You know the drill.
Let me monologue
a little first
and hold off
on showing the guns,
unless they get heroic.
Come on.
How's that Pontiac
treating you?
Can't complain.
Yeah, well, I told you
she was reliable.
They'll spend a couple
weeks spinning their wheels,
trying to decrypt the data. Once
that fails, we'll try and collect
all the paper records
from the local town halls
and banks
across the country.
Titles, deeds, loan records,
bank statements...
that's our target.
I know which
teams at E Corp
will be tasked with this
and their procedures.
I'm gonna assume by your funny
accent that you're Tyrell Wellick
Who the fuck are you?
I wouldn't.
Mr. Wellick, I'm gonna
need you to answer some questions.
Did anyone see you come here'?
Mr. Wellick?
Does anyone know
you're here now'?
No.
Is that
your SUV out there?
Yeah.
I'm gonna need the keys.
What the fuck is this?
I will get to you
in a moment.
Come on, Mr. Wellick.
My requests have
been pretty simple so far.
Phone, too.
Do you know
how to drive?
Yes or no question.
Yes.
Good. I'm gonna need you to
drive to, uh, 17th and 6th.
Drop his car off
at the parking lot there.
Put this on the dash.
Go ahead.
And leave.
Make sure no one sees you.
And then go home
and lie low.
Okay'? All right, Mr. Wellick,
come on. Let's go.
No one's going anywhere
until you tell me what...
If you're seeing me, that
means you boys fucked up.
Apparently, your friend,
James, E Corp IT, I believe...
After he completed
your honeypot request,
he contacted
a Gideon Goddard,
who reported
the incident to the FBI,
and then, well...
Do I really need
to go any further?
From what I understand, tonight
got a little sloppy joes,
if I'm being kind,
which I am.
And if I say no'?
Mr. Wellick,
pretty soon you're gonna be the
most wanted man in the world.
There will most likely
be a manhunt,
the likes of which we
haven't seen since bin Laden,
given what
you two did tonight.
Now, lam your only shot
at staying out of jail.
But, hey, if you want to try to
make a go of it on your own,
well, that's on you.
I'll hightail it out of here
quicker than you can
finish a box of Swedish Fish.
You should go.
How long do I
have to be here?
Not sure.
If you absolutely need
to contact your wife,
we have secure
ways of doing it.
Just give me
some time to work on it.
No. No contact.
If I'm gonna be here
for a while,
the more distance I create,
the-the better it is for me
the better
it is for her.
That's the only way I'm
gonna make it through this.
All right.
Well, I'll check in on you
every couple days,
make sure you're okay.
You're leaving? So what...
what about Elliot?
We have work to do.
I'm told that's
being worked on.
I'll need my gun back.
If I'm gonna be here alone,
I'll need protection.
We own 37 acres
of the surrounding property,
all enclosed
by ground sensors
and IR motion cameras,
wrought-iron gates.
This place is like
a chastity belt.
Nothing's gettin' in.
You want to be protected,
don't leave the property.
Elliot Alderson.
Are you Elliot Alderson?
Mr. Alderson, you're
under arrest
for unauthorized
use of a computer,
computer trespassing,
grand larceny...
And I would be
the greatest job president,
ever, in my opinion.
So, this is
your house.
One of your houses,
I assume.
I've never been
to this island.
You know, it doesn't
even show up on Google Maps.
You're going back
to New York in 22 minutes.
Well, Jesus Christ,
you could've called me
instead of putting me
on a four-hour flight.
I got a bad L4.
I need you to start an image
rehabilitation on Tyrell Wellick.
He's an ex-E Corp employee
who's about to be blamed
for the Five/Nine hack.
No matter how public it gets,
it is important that he stays
in a positive light.
Any chance Obama
goes after him?
People love to defend
anything he hates.
Also, there's a new narrative
I would like you to explore.
I need you to put fsociety's
origin on Iranian soil.
Iran, huh?
That's brown enough.
Shouldn't be too hard.
One last thing...
I may have a potential
candidate for president
I want you to back.
Now, I've created
tens of thousands of jobs
over my career,
tens of thousands.
Look, the country's desperate right now.
But you can't be serious.
I mean, the guy's
a buffoon.
He's completely divorced from reality.
How would you even control him?
If you pull
the right strings,
a puppet will dance
any way you desire.
Right? Make America
great again.
I say it.
Max, he's interfering
with the resonator bomb.
Stop him!
I checked all the elevators,
Max, it's not here.
It's got to be. Keep looking.
Mr. Wellick?
I'm Mr. Williams.
Please, come, come.
Have a seat.
Would you like some tea?
I brought Soderblandning
just for you.
No, I'm fine.
Are you comfortable here?
You have everything
you need?
No.
I've been here
four days by myself.
What's going on?
Where's Elliott?
Where Elliot is
is an interesting story,
and I've been tasked to come
here precisely for that reason
to explain it to you.
Please sit.
First,
I have a few questions.
We understand you
were working with Elliot...
On Stage 2
before your bad luck.
Is that correct?
Yes.
And we need
to get started on it.
E Corp might've already begun
the recovery program.
We need to start
our research.
We can't squander
our lead time like this.
Four days is already too long.
Yes, well...
before we commit
our resources to you,
I was sent here to confirm
your loyalty to our cause.
This is something we take
very seriously
if we're to work
with someone at this level.
You mean the Dark Army?
Of course, I will
be loyal to you.
You're our partners...
Did you kill Sharon Knowles'?
What?
Did you kill
Sharon Knowles?
I'm not sure I understand.
Don't look away.
Look at me. Did you
kill Sharon Knowles?
What does this have
to do with...
Did you kill Sharon Knowles'?
No.
Do you love your wife?
What is this?
Of course, I do!
Have you slept with anyone else
since you've been married?
Don't look away.
Look at me.
Have you slept with anyone else
since you've been married?
No.
Will you be loyal to me?
Yes.
Were you fired from E Corp?
No, I quit.
Are you afraid
of becoming your father'?
What?
Do you hate your father?
No.
Will you be loyal to me?
Yes.
Did you murder
Sharon Knowles?
This is enough!
Did you murder Sharon Knowles?
I said no!
Do you hate your father?
No.
Do you love your wife?
Of course I do.
Were you fired?
No.
Will you be loyal to me?
Yes!
Don't look away. Look at me.
Do you hate your father'?
Are you afraid
of becoming your father'?
This is enough.
Were you fired from E Corp?
This is enough!
Did you murder Sharon Knowles?
Will you be loyal to me?
Yes!
Have you slept
with anyone else
since you've been married?
Have you slept with anyone else
YES.
Have you ever cheated
on your wife?
No.
Do you hate your father?
Yeah.
Were you fired
from E Corp?
Yeah.
Are you afraid
of becoming your father'?
YES.
Did you murder
Sharon Knowles?
Yes, yes, yes.
Will you be loyal to me?
No, I will not.
I will not.
But I will always
be loyal to Elliot.
You'll need to prep
Stage 2 from here
until we establish a more
permanent headquarters.
We'll get you everything you
need to begin reconnaissance.
You'll receive
a phone and a laptop
with a VSAT to a satellite
that we control.
Further instructions
will follow.
We're naming this op
Red Wheelbarrow.
It was Mr. Alderson's request.
But you still
haven't told me...
where is Elliot?
You have a collect call
from an inmate
at the Queensboro
Correctional Facility.
This call will be recorded
and monitored.
Please press one to accept.
Hello?
Is it really you?
Who is this?
Bonsoir, Elliot.
“Death Likes It Hot“
by Gore Vidal. Chapter one.
The death of Peaches Sandoe,
the midget,
at the hands, or rather feet...
In the sideshow of the circus
at Madison Square Garden...
You seem frustrated.
It was Elliot.
He was acting strange.
Doesn't exactly floor me.
Come outside with me
for a moment.
Get a firm stance.
Solid grip.
Swing through the log!
I need to get back to work.
You know,
if you're not careful,
you can lose your mind
up here alone.
This is the best way
to get you centered.
Balance is key.
Let me walk you
through another one.
I used to do it
as a child.
Why'd you ever stop?
Because I hated it.
Even better.
Here's the femtocell.
The malware's
already installed.
Just need you to mod it and do
your thing with the antennas.
Cool. I'll hit
this up tonight.
Tonight?
Try now, kid.
We're on a schedule.
We have some worrywarts
back at the house.
Training Angela for this hack
has been a hitch.
What's up?
You're acting weird.
You ever think about not
doing this shit anymore?
Just giving it up?
I mean, can't we
just be a normal couple
that complains
about the water bill
and looks up vacation
packages to... Budapest?
I knew I should've
never let you fuck me.
Okay.
I'm joking, dickface.
Look, we're in the eye
of a shitstorm,
and it ain't
slowing down right now.
But it will.
Maybe then
we can discuss Budapest.
She's antsy for it, so...
make sure you get it back
to me soon.
She's a job.
Always was.
If anything gets fucked up,
she's protected, you're not.
Why are you
telling me this'?
Stop caring
about her.
Trust me.
Bye.
That thing needs to go back
to the city, ASAP.
There's additional
code on here.
The Android malware... this has
nothing to do with our plan.
Why am I even discussing
this with you?
Elliot and I should be
working on this together.
If we were in the same room,
this would've been done.
Are you finished?
How you holding up'?
Thought this might
cheer you up.
Help remind you
of the old country.
Swedish Fish.
I take it you've read the news
of your wife's divorce.
Listen, don't believe
everything you read, okay'?
Those tabloids...
they're always full of shit.
Look how they almost ruined
Richard Gem's life,
and he's a damn
fine actor.
Primal Fear, am I right'?
"No one who's been emasculated
by crushing or cutting
may enter the assembly
of the Lord."
Deuteronomy 23:1.
Hey.
Thanks for getting
me the sunglasses.
Freeze! Don't move!
Let me see your hands.
Hands in the air, now!
Yep, I'm looking
at him right now.
Yes, sir.
I have the coordinates
plugged into my GPS.
I should be there
in about an hour.
Yes, sir. U-FAP.
We'll keep this on lockdown.
Okay, Mr. Wellick,
I need to let you know
that you're being
detained locally by me
from unlawful flight
to avoid prosecution.
I'll be transferring
you to FBI custody,
where you'll be
federally charged.
I can't believe it's actually
you. I just had a hunch.
Do you speak English?
You just got me
a promotion, you know that?
Before the FBI takes you away, I
got to get a selfie with you.
No one's gonna believe this.
You all right'?
Finally.
I was thinking you guys
were gonna send the cavalry.
You guys and your goddamn
cute puzzles.
I could've gotten here sooner if
you just gave me the address.
I had to solve a fucking
math problem to figure it out.
You're lucky
I covered the area
and made sure all the leads on
Wellick came directly to me.
But I wasn't planning
on killing a fucking cop.
What if he had called it in
to the local Barney Fife?
I mean, if you had
done your job...
You got to understand
where I'm coming from.
Now, lam getting
some serious heat at work,
which in my world
eventually leads to suspicion.
Suspicion because
of the events
you guys created.
I dodged a shootout in China.
That hasn't gone unnoticed.
Why was there a shootout?
Who the fuck knows?
Because your boss is a maniac.
And now,
with this FBI hack,
it's left us in a shitstorm
over Berenstain.
Shit happens.
Today wasn't our best day,
but we took care of it.
"We"?
I took care of it.
Yeah. Right.
I forgot.
You guys don't give
a shit about me.
Make sure this
doesn't happen again.
You fucking weirdo.
Hey, don't mind him.
He's a little snake. You know,
the kind of guy that will...
slice your throat
when you fart.
So...
you want to tell me
what that was all about,
running off like that?
You and I, our stories
aren't that different.
I'm not wanted
for the crime of the century.
I work a little
more subtly.
But we're both married
to our jobs...
Whether by nature
or by choice.
That said...
my boys were
everything to me.
Problem is,
I fucked up.
Took too long
to realize it.
And when my wife left me,
she took 'em.
What happened?
I was lost.
As lost as
you are right now.
And after chopping
a fuckload of wood myself,
I realized I needed them
in my life.
But I knew I had
to have a lot of patience.
And when the time
was right...
I was able to prove to my wife
that I was a good provider,
a good father,
a good man.
Now, tonight,
when I get home, my kids
are gonna run up and hug me.
We're gonna make Jiffy Pop and
watch Big Brother together.
When all is said
and done here,
you'll have your chance
to fix your situation.
And then your wife and son
will come running
up to greet you
at the end
of a long day's work.
My wife has to see me
as someone strong again.
She has to know
I will fix this.
But we have to get
this mission back on track.
And that can't happen
until Elliot and I
are reunited.
Give me a few more weeks,
and I promise...
you'll see him.
Couldn't close?
Nah, he walked.
What happened?
I'll tell you
what happened.
You couldn't
relate to him.
Take my thermos,
for example.
Yeah, so what? You
don't even have kids.
Point is, people
want a connection.
Makes you
more trustworthy.
You walk around with one of
these, and all of a sudden,
you're that corny guy
who's proud of being a father,
helps them buy
what you're selling.
Yeah. I'm gonna go in
for the night.
Next time,
make the sale.
James, you are evicted
from the Big Brother House.
Should we make out?
It's been really fun.
So how'd it go?
It was cool.
Got to stab up a bunch of
neo-Nazi motherfuckers to death.
You know, not that I'm a fan
of murderin' and shit,
'cause I respect life and all,
but when it come
to nee-Nazis...
Well, shit,
not gonna lie,
it was kind of fun.
I mean how'd it go
with Alderson?
Oh.
He got his papers.
Should be out soon.
By the way, get him laid
when he gets out, man.
Homeboy is wound tighter
than a chinchilla's asshole.
Go get packed.
He's being released.
It's perfect. He will love it.
Now, I'm giving this
back to you
for safe keeping.
The barrel was
jammed. Squib load.
Next shot would've blown
your hand clean off.
Lucky for you,
I took care of it.
So this is how
the meet's gonna go down.
We've reached out to Elliot, and you
will be given further instructions
as soon as he makes contact.
Until then, we're gonna
need you to stay here
so you'll be near
the rendezvous point.
Now, you'll give
our driver the address.
He won't know where you're
going until you tell him.
If you get hungry,
just call for room service.
Stay away from
the windows, okay?
We can't take any chances
now that we're in the city.
Okay.
Wait.
What about my suit?
Tyrell, we discussed this.
I need it.
It's nonnegotiable.
I have to look
my best for him.
It's in your closet.
I still strongly
advise against wearing it.
You know, this isn't
bumfuck nowhere.
You get picked up around here,
we can't protect you.
Mr. Willick, it sounds like
someones here downstairs.
I'll be right down.
You Elliot?
How do you know my name'?
No Elliot?
No, no, okay. Wait.
Chambers and Church.
We have to be careful now.
They said he's going
to be okay.
You need to sit down.
When he wakes up,
you shouldn't talk to him.
I will handle this.
He should be in a hospital.
The conditions here
aren't suitable.
It's...
He's in good hands.
I don't understand.
He and I were
meant to be a team,
but he kept saying
I wasn't real.
He said he didn't see me, but I was
standing right in front of him.
We were talking.
So why would he say
I wasn't real, hmm?
I don't understand.
I just don't understand.
It was almost as if
he were a different person.
Tyrell...
He is...
Tyrell.
There's something that I need
to tell you about Elliot.
You're right.
He sometimes can become
a different person.