Hello?
Bonsoir, Elliot.
They're planning something.
17 of 71 facilities
around the country so far.
This is where the
paper records are going.
Elliot, what
is Stage 2'?
The femtocell was to
get access to their UPS's.
They're trying to blow up Evil
Corp's recovery buifdfn g.
I don't play fair.
I play what I want.
I invoke my Fifth Amendment.
You're an
enemy combatant.
You don't
have any rights.
One of your
patients hacked me.
He stole my dog
on top of it.
The phone call...
make me understand.
I wanted you
to feel what I felt.
You pussy.
You...
This fucker thinks
he can hurt my girl!
If you're serious about
punishing him... I am.
Just tell me what to do.
The E Corp party.
When you saw Scott,
he was disheveled.
Yeah, but Joanna...
Tell the cops your story.
Scott Knowles intimidated you.
This is how we punish him.
That ever-looming
presence
that is Mr. Robot,
I don't feel it.
Is it possible that the
bullet killed him...
And not me?
I need to find a way
to fix what I did.
I need a job at Evil Corp.
You know when
you fuck something up
and you wish you had the
power to hit "undo"?
Like when you say the dumbest thing
in front of your biggest crush.
or when you talk shit
about your boss in an email,
then hit "reply all"
to everyone at work.
Or when you crash
the entire world economy
and kick-start
the inevitable downfall
of human civilization?
We all have those days.
But today is not
gonna be one of them.
Because today
I found a way
to hit "undo."
Today is the day I start
working at Evil Corp.
Hello. I'm Linda,
Chief Human Resources Officer
here at Evil Corp.
Evil Corp is,
well, evil.
That much I thought, but
what I didn't realize was
maybe they're
a necessary evil
that just needs
to be kept in check.
In fact, maybe
calling them evil
was just my dorm room
philosophizing run amuck.
I'd like to say welcome
to the Evil Corp family.
We're happy
to have you here.
But this doesn't mean
I'm selling out.
I'm just growing HP-
Signing up for a 401K,
choosing an HMO plan
with a good deductible.
Sign up for Trunk Club.
Pop a few Zoloft.
Join in on the
live-action cartoon
of 2D emotions that
everyone else is in.
I finally see the fatal
exception error of my ways,
and I know what to do now.
I'm gonna fix
the world I broke,
and put it back together
better than it was before.
Let's talk about your crucial
role here at Evil Corp.
I'm gonna
undo the hack.
Now, I can't decrypt
the data I fucked up,
that much is true.
But since I'm working
on the recovery team,
I can help them
rebuild the database
and defend the fort
at the same time.
There's a little talent
roaming around on this floor,
but the primo poon
is on floor 31.
As of last week, it
looks like Tyrell was right.
Evil Corp has delivered
their paper records
from 17 of their 71 buildings
to their New York facility.
Pretty sure she would cheat
on her fiance for me, man.
She really, like, the way she
looks at me, dude, it's like,
slippery when wet,
am I right?
But lucky for
them, now they've got me.
Our current plan is deeply flawed
and massively inefficient.
This is William.
He's my technology manager.
If I can convince him
to convince his boss
to convince her boss
to digitize all the paper records
in their local facilities
instead of shipping
them here, then...
We can avoid a single
point of failure.
We would install
hardware and softw...
Elliot, I hear
your passion,
but I got tickets to the Goo
Goo Dolls reunion concert
tonight, so let's wrap this up.
Okay?
His password was
pretty easy to figure out.
After going
through his emails,
I quickly learned that
he was having the engineers
install rootkits on
all of Evil Corp's phones,
so they can illegally sell
private consumer data.
I tipped off the FBI,
got him arrested, and
promptly set a meeting
with the next exec
up the chain.
But meetings can take
forever to set.
So in the meantime, I had
to look for a stopgap.
In this case, E Shipping, their
shipping management console.
Wait a minute,
this ain't right.
All our shipments are
supposed to go to New York.
The paper says “Sioux
Falls, South Dakota."
Yeah, you're in
Sioux Falls, Earl,
which sure as shit
don't make no sense.
But all right.
Unpack her, boys!
I'm sending
shipping requests
to the actual facilities,
but in the manifest,
I'm making it look like
all the paper's still
arriving in New York.
It'll take a while, but I
just need to buy enough time
until I can prove my case
to upper management.
By eliminating physical
paper delivery,
we can cut E Shipping cost, installing
hardware and software at...
Elliot, you are ambitious,
I'll give you that,
but I got a SoulCycle
class I'm late for.
Let's pick this up
sometime next quarter?
Hacking Peter was
as easy as watching him.
I felt bad
taking him down,
until I saw that he had
his engineering team
use special software
to help E Cam's
auto manufacturing partners
cheat the emissions test
to hide how much pollution
they really created.
Factoring in the
bureaucracy and the line of
corrupt, moronic managers
I have to get through,
I'll need lo keep up the illusion
that shipments are still happening.
These are the same damn
boxes you brought last week.
You know me. I do
what the paper says.
All right!
Pack it up, boys!
Problem with my illusion is,
what if Tyrell and the Dark Army
think all the records
actually get there?
This is why I gotta keep
the UPS systems safe too,
because these innocuous
backup batteries
in the New York facility
can turn into idle bombs
with the right malware.
And these are
the frontline soldiers
trusted to protect them.
You guys gonna stop me?
I'm a bloodhound, girl.
I just dove right back
in, dude, just... Ah.
This patch ensures
that the UPS devices
will only run trusted code that's
digitally signed by Evil Corp.
Bottom line, even if they think
all the paper records got here,
they won't be able
to blow up that building.
In conclusion,
digitizing locally
and not shipping
paper records here,
is the best option for
our recovery efforts.
Perfect.
Let's set a meeting with
the VP of Technology.
I want to get this
in front of him.
Great work, Elliot.
Once upper
management's on board,
we'll be on our way
to rebuilding the database
and the hack will
officially be behind us.
Doesn't mean that
in my spare time I can't
find ways to purge Evil
Corp of all their shitbags.
You know, your typical
subprime mortgage scammers,
Ponzi schemers...
Pension embezzlers,
and sexual harassers.
That way, when Evil Corp
gets back on its feet,
they'll no longer be evil.
We're proud to call you
a new member of Evil... E Corp.
Because changing the world
was never about tearing E Corp down.
It's about
making them better.
Maybe I fucked up an
already fucked-up world,
but I'm fixing it now,
hitting “undo. “
And, friend,
it feels great.
Okay,
if I'm being real,
I haven't
fixed everything.
The loneliness
came back.
Worse than I remember.
I don't get it.
I know I'm doing
the right thing.
You have to see that.
Then what is this?
Why do I feel this
empty void inside?
Even Zoloft
isn't helping.
I don't know
what to do.
Fuck.
What's wrong with me?
I'm really starting to lose it.
With everything going on,
my landlord at the office
hasn't been paying utilities
or maintenance, so...
I'll be working from my
home office for a while.
Am I supposed
to say something?
It's a nice rug.
Thank you.
How are you feeling about
your birthday today?
Shit.
She's right.
Totally forgot.
It is my
birthday today.
Do you have
plans tonight?
Umm, no.
In our
last session,
we talked about
your sister.
We haven't
been talking.
Can I ask why?
She's one of the
reasons he comes out.
Talk about that.
Well, he's...
been gone, right'?
He hasn't come out since I
stopped talking to her.
How does that
make you feel,
that he's not
around anymore'?
It's different.
It's better.
For everyone.
You're still not
answering the question.
How do you feel?
Good.
You miss him,
don't you?
It's okay
if you do.
I miss being a
part of something.
Being a part
of what, exactly?
Something
important.
That meant
something.
Where'd you go?
I remembered this time
Darlene and I...
Never mind.
I'd love
to hear it,
if you don't
mind sharing it.
When we were kids,
this one year, there was
this huge snowstorm.
And Darlene and I
were so excited.
And we spent all
day just playing outside.
We made this snowman,
and we called him...
Kevin McAllister,
you know, the kid
from Home Alone.
We were pretty obsessed
with that movie.
We even did the hands to the face,
like how he does in the movie.
And how'd
that turn out?
He just looked
like a snowman with...
no arms and
weird cheeks.
And we were so proud
of it, we promised
we'd steal my dad's camera and
take a picture of it
before it melted.
And what happened when
you went back out?
I never got
a chance to.
Why not?
That was the day
of my accident,
when my dad pushed
me out the window.
We were at the hospital
till pretty late.
Your dad pushed you
out a window?
Yeah.
I've told you
that before.
Elliot,
you've never...
No, you've never
told me this.
That's weird.
I remember...
I could have sworn I told you.
There's not much to it.
He pushed me
out the window.
I broke my arm and
went to the hospital.
Kevin melted.
Darlene was pissed.
End of story.
What made you think
of this just now?
I don't know.
ANNOUNCER; Truth bombs are
coming your way, Cody-Hes.
Tonight, please welcome
our special guest,
Joanna Wellick. Thanks
for being here.
Thank you
for having me.
Scott Knowles has, uh,
been facing charges
for murdering his wife,
Sharon Knowles.
Initially, your husband, Tyrell
Wellick, was accused of the murder,
until you claimed
Scott Knowles
confessed to killing
his wife while beating you.
And since then, a bartender
from the night of the party
has also come forward to
corroborate your story.
I know that this must
be difficult for you.
You've been brave
just coming here.
Do you want to tell us a little
more about what happened?
My lawyers have advised
me not to speak to that.
But what I can say,
Frank, is that
I didn't need Scott Knowles
to be arrested to know
that my husband
is innocent.
Mr. Knowles is...
clearly a
troubled man
and has been fixating
on us for some time.
I understand that
you and your son
have been tormented endlessly
by fanatics and paparazzi.
Some even went so far as to
claim you filed for divorce.
I did file for divorce...
a few months ago.
It was a moment
of weakness.
I listened to
the wrong people,
who were convincing me that
that was the right thing to do.
But I have and
always will be
faithful to Tyrell.
I have since dismissed
my petition for divorce.
He is...
the only man
I've ever loved
and the only man
I ever will love.
In times
of chaos and uncertainty,
when the world
feels off balance,
we look to those who've stood
with us from the beginning.
Since 1884, we've
had America's back.
We may get knocked down, but
we'll never be knocked out.
Still on your side.
Breaking news, a new
fsociety video has been released.
Hello, E Corp.
We are fsociety.
We are here
to tell you that
though you survived
our first blow,
you will not
survive our last.
In the coming weeks,
we will be sending you
a message so loud
that it will make
your eardrums explode...
literally.
The clock is ticking.
We are fsociety.
We are malicious
and hostile.
We do not compromise.
You have been warned.
DiPIERRO: It was released
about an hour ago
Six weeks,
you've given us nothing.
And now we have
this to deal with?
That video is bullshit.
DiPIERRO: That video came
from the same Vimeo account
as the last one
you guys used.
Then it has
to be Dark Army.
Cisco probably
gave them access.
But that is not one of our guys,
okay, trust me on this...
You're a CHS.
You understand what
that means, right?
I don't understand half the
letters you guys throw at me.
Confidential
human source.
Cool. Now I get it.
See what speaking English
can accomplish?
Your job is to get intel
from Elliot on Tyrell Wellick.
That is the only reason
you're not in jail right now.
I don't know what you want
me to tell you, dude.
He's not talking
to Tyrell.
How do you
know that?
Five weeks ago, the night
we lost your tail...
And then gave us a
bullshit explanation as to
where you went? Yeah.
Stink on that
still hasn't washed off.
I asked Elliot point-blank,
and he said no.
If you don't
believe me,
bring him in. He'll tell
you the same thing.
You know that telling
Elliot anything about this
would violate the terms
of your immunity.
It would spook his
connection to Tyrell.
Get woke already, dude.
He is not nor has he ever had a
fucking relationship with Tyrell.
June 16, 2015.
This is a call from Queensboro
Correctional Facility.
Hello?
Is it really you?
Who is this?
Bonsoir, Elliot.
You're listening
to '80s XM radio.
You've been looking in the
mirror the whole drive home.
I need to make a stop.
Stay here.
You want to consider
your actions carefully.
She fucking lied to me.
She went on national television
and she said she still loves him.
You love me!
I know you do!
You told me we were
gonna be together.
That's the only reason
I agreed to testify!
You made me lie to the
police to get Tyrell off!
But now I'm gonna
tell them the truth!
Get up.
If you retract your
statement, you will die.
I'm not being overly
emotional about this.
It's just that's how little
we care about your life.
Forget this night
ever happened, move on.
Marry a nice,
young lady
who actually finds
whatever you are charming.
But understand
one thing:
As certain as the pain
you're feeling right now,
there is no option
where you and Joanna ever
see each other again.
ls everything
under control?
Yes, ma'am.
He just needed
a little clarity.
on, okay, okay.
No, no, no, no, no.
DiPIERRO: The shooter
didn't survive.
The driver looks like
he's gonna pull through.
We have someone
down at the hospital,
ready to question,
but he's still in ICU.
This information
is too sensitive
to share
with the public.
We got lucky
we were on the scene
before anyone
saw the body.
What about the baby? Once you
contact the next of kin...
We're not
contacting them.
He's going
to social services.
Don't be soft.
Not now.
Her husband is the most
wanted man in the world.
And you and I both know
that finding him is
more important than
anything else, especially
with that goddamn video
that just got released.
Something about
that video.
I believe Darlene when
she says it's not real.
We have to assume fsociety's
grown past her at this point.
Yeah, but why wouldn't
she just say that then?
Her whole immunity's
based on giving us intel.
Right now all she wants to
do is protect her brother,
who took a job at E Corp
for Lord knows why.
There's no incentive
for her to lie to us.
She didn't even know he
was working with Tyrell.
Why would you
trust her on this?
Because I still think there's
a Dark Army connection here.
We have our other team
looking into them.
Your focus needs to stay
on Tyrell and fsociety.
Guys back at CART are zeroing
in on the guy in the video.
We might have
a good lead soon.
Let's just hope you're
reading your girl right.
I'm worried
she's at flight risk.
No, she's good.
Trust me.
I'm
surprised you came.
Thought you were going the distance
with the silent treatment.
If I remember correctly,
you were the one who told
me to go fuck myself.
Since when did you start
remembering everything so well?
Why'd you text me, Darlene?
What am I doing here?
Wanted to wish you
a happy birthday.
ELLIOT; IS that all?
God, what is
your problem?
Why are you trying
to shut me out?
Because we can't talk.
Why not?
You know why.
Maybe I want to
hear you say it.
Because...
You're my trigger.
What am I, in a fucking
therapy session?
Makes sense.
You're my sister,
part of my childhood.
If I could take back
what happened to Dad, I would.
What happened to him
fucked me up too.
So don't think for a second our
shitty childhood is only yours.
I wish Dad were
here right now.
He'd know what to do.
I'm leaving.
First thing
in the morning,
I'm gonna crash with
a friend upstate.
I can't do
this anymore.
I can't be here.
Just thought you'd
want to know that.
Spending this last year
with you was never about
whatever the fuck you want
to call what we did.
The real reason
I did all of this
was so that we
could be close again.
I guess that's...
something else I thought
you'd want to know.
You remember when we made Kevin
McAllister, the snowman?
Of course.
Do you... Do you want
to talk about it?
I want you to stay
with me tonight.
I'm good, dude, you don't
have to worry about me.
It's not that.
I don't want
to be alone.
Given the ripple effect
of rapid global inflation,
19 of the 20 members
of this international forum
have signed
the Five/Nine Economic Accord,
making Ecoin the currency
by which all others
will be measured.
The only obstacle
is the illegitimate
monetary imposter
that China has
unofficially adopted...
Bitcoin.
China is weakening
our economic state
by not signing this accord,
and the fact that they
have embraced Bitcoin,
shows their resistance
and emphatic rejection
of our collective attempt
to rescue the global economy.
In short, ladies and
gentlemen...
They are declaring
a currency war.
This has to be brief.
Truthfully, the only reason
I even agreed to meet
was that this room happens
to be on my way out...
Have your government
sign the goddamn accord!
In 11 days, you'll
have what you want.
U.N. vote to annex the Congo,
it's as good as yours,
but this currency
war must end.
The rest of the world needs
China to embrace Ecoin now.
We're at risk of other
countries pulling out.
Let me put this
as simply as I can,
so that we never have to
belabor this point again.
Your success will
always follow mine.
I don't give a fuck
about your accord.
Until I get my U.N. vote,
don't waste my time.
Or maybe in 11 days,
the administration changes its
mind about your precious U.N. vote
I worked so hard
to procure for you.
Your empty threat
reminds me
that there's something
I never shared with you.
My associates found
your pet employee
after she smuggled out
documents on
the Washington
Township plant.
Now that I've gotten
a chance to talk to her,
I can see
why you like her.
She makes a very
good companion.
And those eyes of hers...
I contemplated firing a
bullet into each of them,
but they're just
so hypnotizing.
Don't mistake
my generosity
for generosity.
What are you doing?
Why are you awake?
It's early.
You're not answering
my question.
What were you doing
by my computer?
I saw you
behind the monitor.
Jesus, I was
looking for a pen.
To write you a note. What's
with the fucking paranoia'?
A note for what?
I'm leaving. I have
to catch my bus.
The buses
aren't running.
There's a transportation strike,
it's all over the news.
Okay, the train then. What's
with the interrogation?
You were gonna leave
without saying good-bye.
Thus, the note.
And here I thought we were
in a good fucking place
after last night.
You're not answering
my fucking question.
Why are you here?
What do you mean?
You invited me.
Jesus. It's you.
What'd you do
with the computer'?
Why did you sleep here
last night?
You're scaring me...
Answer me!
Are you serious, Elliot?
You're hurting me. Stop!
Answer me!
Why...
Stop!
Stay the fuck away from
me, you fucking psycho.
So
how does it work?
How does what work?
If I wanted you
to talk to him.
What happened?
Did he come back?
I need you
to talk to him.
Didn't you say
that that could help'?
Everyone's case
is different.
But yes,
I think this
can help you.
What do we do?
Let's just take a moment.
Why don't you
sit back and relax?
I'd like you
to close your eyes.
Take a deep breath.
Listen to the sound
of my voice.
If you want me
to talk to him,
just let him
come to me.
Give him permission.
Elliot?
You should know
that nothings gonna come from this.
We were doing just fine.
Ifs nice
to finally meet you.
This was better when I could
just come and go as I pleased,
when we were whole.
Now I'm seeing things
that he should be seeing too.
We're just getting
torn apart.
You need to leave us alone so I
can get him back to our work.
Elliot never told me
how attractive you are.
You know, for a shrink,
you're, uh, pretty foxy.
Thank you, but... I'm more
interested in talking about you.
Come on.
Never thought about it?
Getting with one
of your patients?
That would cross some
ethical boundaries for me.
Sucks for you.
Everybody knows
crazy can be sexy.
So you think
you're crazy'?
Relax.
It's a figure
of speech.
Can I ask
for your name?
Well, what does
he call me?
Mr. Robot.
Seriously?
He still
calls me that?
Talk about labels.
I'd like to talk about
why you're here.
"A civilization which leaves
so many of its citizens"
"unsatisfied and
drives them into revolt"
"neither has nor
deserves the prospect"
"of a lasting existence."
Who said that?
Freud.
Wow. Beautiful and smart.
Sorry.
As beautiful as you are, you're
not getting inside my head.
Why not?
Because before you found out
about me, we were good.
I'm trying
to help him.
You're not trying
You're trying
to destroy me.
I'm not trying
to destroy you.
Quite the opposite,
actually.
I want to understand you.
You understand shit.
You're just another
phony cooze playing friend.
It doesn't matter
anymore anyway.
Because of her,
we've been compromised.
She compromised us,
and Elliot didn't see it.
What do you mean,
you've been compromised?
I'm done
talking to you.
ELLIOT; Krista?
When are we
gonna start?
What happened?
Were you there?
Did you go with me
or stay with him?
What did you see?
What did Mr. Robot mean,
"We've been compromised"?
You were there, you heard
it along with her, right?
What was Mr. Robot
talking about?
Scan my QR code
and I'll suck your dick.
Who compromised us?
Who's even us?
Him and me?
Or him and Tyrell?
No, he couldn't still
be working with Tyrell.
Could he?
ls Stage 2 still on?
No, I would know.
That's impossible.
Stage 2 is down.
I made sure of it.
Who compromised me?
And why do I suddenly
feel so alive?
How do you do it?
How do you
get so lucky'?
Even when the world's
going to shit,
you're sitting pretty.
The truth is,
I never gave
a shit about the dog.
In fact,
I hate the dog.
Vet bills are
through the roof
because this little
piece of shit is sick.
She's been shitting all
over my house for weeks.
It's probably dying.
Figured you wanted
her so badly,
let her shit all
over your house.
Like you did mine.
Good job.
Stage 2.
I want it to happen
on the day of the U.N. vote.
Whether it goes
our way or not.
Sir, Stage 2 is only
meant to be implemented
if Price doesn't
come through.
If the U.N. approves our
annexation of the Congo,
we can finally
move our operation
to the country's
Luwow mine.
Why would you still
want to carry this out,
given the
serious implications?
Ifs time Phillip Price's
hand got slapped.
DiPIERRO: Last time I buy
from that coffee shop.
They only take Ecoin.
Gotta use Ecoin.
With the exchange rate,
dollar's worth shit now.
DiPIERRO: You get anything
from Elliot's computer?
He hasn't
logged in all day.
Last night he sent an
encrypted email with a link.
Could be lucky, could be
sending it to Tyrell, right?
Is this from
last night?
Oh, also
I was able to get
a clean audio recording
of his place.
Seriously?
Yeah.
He dropped some good intel.
Here, let me play it for you.
That'll be stuck in
my head all day now.
DiPIERRO: Turn it Off.
Is that coming
from downstairs?
Yeah, that's
Darlene's apartment, but...
who the fuck is that?
Is Darlene home?
No, she's out.
You think she told
someone about the safe house?
DiPIERRO: This email he sent
from his computer,
did you go to this link?
Yeah, downloaded
the file, opened it,
but didn't find anything.
This email
isn't for Tyrell.
It's for us.