71 buildings owned by
E Corp exploded or caught fire.
All those people who died.
They think the total
will be over 4,000.
What are you doing?
See? They all came back.
[thought
I would never win.
Not until I met Whiterose.
Don't think for a second
that I don't know
that you're keeping
something from me.
No, no, no.
Listen to me.
You have to stop the attack!
Your wife's dead,
which means that your son
is currently being raised
at Peaceful Acres Foster Care.
If you're thinking about
telling anyone here about me,
you won't live to place
a flower at your wife's grave.
But we still haven't
discussed the coltan mines.
The fucking Congo can wait.
It's time Phillip Price's hand
got slapped.
If the UN approves
our annexation of the Congo,
we can finally move
our operation.
My actions were never
meant to harm E Corp.
Trust me' it will survive.
But I won't.
Mr. Alderson can die for us,
just like his father.
Something ain't right about this guy.
I don't trust him.
TRENTON; If what I discovered is
real, do you know what that means?
We could potentially
undo this whole thing.
If anything does happen to us,
I sent the e-mail to go out
automatically to someone I trust.
Maybe there still are
things left for me to do.
Evil Corp is 80%
of our business.
If we lose them,
it's gonna be it for us.
It's gonna be it for me.
Allsafe officially opened
its doors in '04.
We have a relatively
small roster,
but that way our clients
have unprecedented access,
our undivided attention...
All those are standards
E Corp expects
from any vendor we hire.
Terry, please.
Let him continue.
Allsafe has several
other clients
also in the Fortune 100.
And when called upon,
we help them out
in some pretty sticky
incident response scenarios.
We'll be making a bit
of a splash next month
when we release
our 2012 report.
That's all teddy bears
and hand jobs,
but what are your financials?
We can't wake up one day
and find ourselves tits up,
dicks blowing in the breeze.
Well, yes.
Of course, of course.
Thank you, Angela.
Hey, hon,
you want to top me off?
And add a pinch of Sweet'N
Low, but not too much.
Angela, my assistant
can handle that. It's okay.
No, no. It's okay.
Regarding
our financials, Mr. Colby,
this will correspond
to page eight.
Well, that was a cute
field trip, Phillip.
Next time I waste
an afternoon, though,
I'd prefer a happy ending.
Now what's the real
angle here'?
We headed to Legz & Lae
for happy hour?
We're gonna hire them.
Set the deal in motion
immediately.
What... I...
I don't understand.
Is there something bigger
behind the scenes here
we should know about, or...
I want the contract executed
as soon as possible.
Mr. Price, if I may...
I'm hesitant to depend
on Allsafe
as our security
operation center.
I'm confident I could lead
a team
to establish our own
internal SOC.
And with the appropriate
resources...
I'm sorry, Mister, uh...
Wellick.
Wellick! Mr. Wellick!
I'm sorry if I misled you
into thinking that I was
seeking your counsel
or approval,
because I most certainly
am not.
Understood.
Good.
Just hope it doesn't
come back to haunt us.
This decision has been made.
Remember
to alert the Bureau
if you're going to leave
the city, Mr. Wellick.
And no international travel
for now.
Mr. Robot.
He took over again.
“They own the FBI. "
What is he trying to say?
Who's they?
Dark Army. It's gotta be.
Fuck, I left my machine
unlocked.
Trenton's e-mail.
Did he see this?
If he did, he knows
that Trenton was close
to finding a way
to undo Five/Nine,
and that I'm gonna finish
what she started.
He also looked up info
on Tyrell Wellick's release.
Why?
What exactly did Mr. Robot
do last night?
Seventy-one buildings.
Was it worth it'?
Get the fuck out of my home.
Gotta say, your revised plan
was batshit insane.
It was supposed to be only one
building, but what you did...
I did what had to be done.
You mean
what they told you to do.
What'd they promise you, huh?
Money?
This isn't about them. This
is about when you fucked me!
I lost everything
because of you.
My son's taken to Denmark,
and my wife's dead!
Okay.
Okay, I can't say that it's
all been smooth sailing,
but you gotta see
the big picture!
There is no big picture!
There was a job,
and I fulfilled my duty,
and that's more
than I can say for you.
Oh, come on.
You know damn well
that's not how
the Dark Army works.
You don't go from most wanted
man on the planet
to hero unless they have
plans for you,
how can you not see that?
The things I did,
the things I sacrificed,
I earned my freedom.
That's the least
they could give me.
Horseshit. You're being added
to a collection of puppets.
No Puppet, no puppet.
You're the puppet!
Wake up! You made a deal with a
force that's bigger than you!
When the time comes,
they're gonna ask you to pay
what they feel you owe them!
This is a childish conspiracy!
Childish? Who's the one
who said we were gods, huh?
Time to grow up.
There are no gods.
Our closest deities
are a society of the richest,
most influential men
in existence.
I'm done with this.
Men who
fuck over the rest of us
for profit,
for fun, and then leave us
in the streets for dead.
Just like your Joanna!
You don't talk about my wife.
Wouldn't she want you to
realize the truth and fight?
Or would she want you
to be their little bitch?
There you go. Fight!
That's the Tyrell
who's been missing.
Now you want
to stop them, too,
before they put you
in that choke collar?
Unless you're into
that sort of thing.
What?
Oh, hello, sir.
May I come in'?
Oh, shit.
Didn't mean to interrupt.
Good evening, Mr. Alderson.
Please join us.
After all, you were a part
of this too.
It's weird,
being here again.
Like we've come
to that slow glide
at the end
of a roller coaster.
We're coming full circle.
Darlene and Mr. Robot
started this whole thing,
and now she and I
are gonna end it.
Trenton was investigating
Romero ever since
she found out he was
monitoring our machines.
This is big.
Why'd she send this to you?
I don't know.
If Trenton's right,
and encryption keys were exported
the night of the hack, then...
There's a chance we can
recover all of E Corp's data.
If we can find those keys.
Why would Romero do this?
There was never supposed
to be a Plan B,
that was the whole point.
This hack was supposed
to be all in.
He did it for the reason
we need those keys now,
in case our revolution failed.
We need access
to his keylogger files.
The feds confiscated
his drives.
Now all of his data is in the
FBI evidence storage system.
Sentinel, yeah,
I know it well.
That's why I'm here.
I need you to give me all the
intel you have about the FBI.
You do realize this isn't
Angela batting her lashes
at some feds to drop
a femtocell
at their E Corp office?
Sentinel is the Fort Knox
of closed networks.
And you want us to just
waltz in there and...
Not us.
Me. I'm gonna do it.
Did you not hear me?
You will get busted.
I don't care how good
you think you are.
The only way we do this
is if I go to them.
I'll hit up my contact...
We can't trust them.
The Dark Army owns the FBI.
How do you know that?
Doesn't matter.
Going to them isn't an option.
I might have an angle.
No, I told you...
I spent the last two months
working with the feds.
I know how they operate.
I'm miles ahead of you
on this.
Okay? I can do this.
What's your angle?
My angle is you trust me.
You gotta promise me.
Any sign of trouble,
you bail.
Even if we do this,
do you really think
it'll make a difference?
I mean the whole world
has gone to shit.
And we did that.
All we can do now is rebuild.
At least that's a start.
And the Dark Army?
You think they're just gonna be
painting each other's toenails
while we go and undo
everything they've worked for'?
You just worry
about getting into Sentinel.
Let me worry
about the Dark Army.
Believe me now'?
Lovely lady like you
with a Taurus?
I don't think so.
It's not a good fit.
But this baby, huh?
It's nice.
Bang a left up here.
I hear you're looking
to barter a TAG Heuer?
My ex-husband's.
I'm sure we can arrange
a deal.
And I really want to feel
you pump the gas here.
Let her open up.
Yeah?
Doesn't that feel good?
on.
Is this supposed to...
I think it's dead.
You know what? Coast her to the
shoulder here on the left.
I'll check things out.
on board computer's so smart,
it probably senses something.
What are you doing?
You know what to do.
Tell you what,
why don't you stroll
on back to the lot,
peruse those Sonatas.
I'll meet you there
in a second.
Go ahead.
I'm right behind you.
I called OnStar and the cops
are on their way,
so we don't have much time.
I need you to set a meet.
Look kid, I already told you,
we're done...
Stage 3.
What the fuck is Stage 3?
Just do what you do and set
the meet with Whiterose.
Since when do I take
orders from you?
If you don't move on this,
it'll be on you
to tell your employer
why you fucked
with their timeline.
Hey.
You're late.
I'm surprised you agreed
to meet.
Thought you weren't allowed
one on ones.
Technically you're not
a source anymore,
so I'll classify this
as a social meet.
But I suggest you get to the
point of why you called.
First, how about
a peace offering?
Shots?
You said you had something
to tell me.
So talk or this is over.
I've been thinking
about our last conversation.
Especially after...
Everything with Trenton
and Mobley,
and you were right.
There are things
I haven't told you.
I'm listening.
Okay, well,
how does this work?
Is this off the record, or am
I fucking my own immunity?
Depends.
Everything you said,
you were on point.
Whiterose was behind
everything.
Five/Nine, the Dark Army
were our partners.
They handled the Chinese side,
we took care of it over here.
And Whiterose,
did you talk to him?
There was a middle man.
If the Dark Army was involved,
then Whiterose
had to greenlight it.
Would you be willing to go on
the record about what you know?
If I testified...
You know what the Dark Army's
capable of.
Darlene, you gotta
rethink this.
We can protect you,
we'll make things right.
Tyrell's walking free,
and your friends are dead.
Do it for them!
Fine. I gotta use
the bathroom.
Fuck...
This is a reminder
that today's city-wide curfew
begins at 9:00 p.m.
this evening
through 4:00 a.m.
tomorrow morning.
Stay indoors
and off the streets.
This is a reminder...
This is proof.
It's finally happening.
We're going back
to the way things should be.
Angela, I want to help you,
but you got to explain to me
what you think is happening.
I can't tell you that.
Only Whiterose can do that.
Whiterose manipulated you.
She exploited your feelings
about your mom,
and used them against you.
That's what she does.
I thought that you wanted
our parents back.
That's never going to happen.
That's because you don't
understand.
We can't talk here.
There are people
that are trying to stop this.
Let's go inside.
I know this may sound
like bullshit,
but I'm sorry I was such
a pain in the ass.
The pressure of trying to find
Tyrell and lying to my brother
and secluding myself in that apartment,
just feeling lonely as shit,
I guess it was just too much.
So this is my long-winded
way of saying I don't think
I have it in me to testify.
Maybe I'm not as cool
and collected as I put on.
I get the front you put up.
It's a trick I use myself.
You are an FBI agent,
yet somehow I feel like you're
the only one I can trust.
Maybe that's because you can.
Yeah. Maybe so.
Okay, well' I hope
the intel helped.
Sorry I couldn't do more.
You're leaving?
Thanks for the drink,
and for listening.
Wait, you want another?
On me?
So you still single?
Wow!
Jumping right into
this conversation again.
Haven't you learned my social
game isn't my strong suit?
Well, I'm willing to bet you've
got some untapped talent.
What's your type?
Where are you going with this?
Well, I am one hell
of a wingwoman, okay?
So let's pick you out one
of these lovelies here.
What about that Ginger?
What, are you not into fire
crotch? Hypocrite.
Dye job.
Fine.
Goth hipster in the corner?
Identity issues.
Oh, okay.
Ooh, what about that?
Oh, my God. Barkeep!
Another round.
'Sup, cuz?
Oh, shit. Sorry, dude.
Don't let me interrupt
your flow or anything,
I mean I didn't know
you had a female caller.
Who's he?
This is why you're asking
about our plan, isn't it?
Angela.
You've been trying to listen
to me, haven't you'?
Did you hear me?
Did you hear
what we were saying out there?
I've just been sitting here,
smoking these trees, girl.
I don't know what the fuck
you talking about.
You're trying to trap me.
Aren't you?
Angela.
You have to leave.
Get out now, trust me.
You've been trying
to trick me.
That's why you wanted me
to explain everything.
It's you who's trying to stop
our plan.
I thought you were on my side.
Dude,
your girl's trippin'.
Look, I don't know
what you guys got going on,
and I'm sorry, sweetheart,
but we really ain't
got the time right now.
We got business to attend to,
and she... She gotta go, bro.
One way or another.
Don't worry, I'm leaving.
You're not going to get any
more information out of me.
Slow your roll, cuz.
We gotta get.
We got a tight schedule
to maintain.
I am here mainly
as a formality, Wellick,
to fake a smile and pretend
to welcome you back.
You have been appointed
CTO at E Corp.
I don't know what to say.
Thank you.
You coming here personally...
Yes, yes. Right, right.
But the direct purpose
of my visit...
I felt it was important
to share with you formally
that the CTO title
is nothing more than that.
You are a mere figurehead
I inherited
from a deal gone wrong.
It happens from time to time.
But I wanted you to understand
the nature of your position
in case you should have
loftier designs.
There'll be none of that.
Obedience will be your only
task at my company.
I worry that could potentially
get awkward
if you thought differently,
so I came here out of respect.
By your silence, I assume
you accept this position?
I know what this is.
You're embarrassed
that you fired me.
There's no shame
in admitting the truth.
You're out of moves
and your company needs me.
E Corp needs my image,
the face of a hero.
That's why you're here.
On, Wellick, Wellick.
It's not that I'm out
of moves.
Its that you're not
worth one.
See you at the office, mm?
Five/Nine, fsociety.
You knew the entire time,
didn't you?
Five/Nine, yes.
Well, not all the minutiae,
of course.
But since the cyber bombings,
the breadcrumbs haven't been
that difficult to follow.
World catastrophes like this,
they aren't caused
by lone wolves like you.
They occur because men
like me allow them.
You just happened
to stumble into one of them.
No, no. I ran the operation.
I pushed the button.
I am the one...
There you go again.
"I, I, I..."
You're still thinking
like alone wolf.
Why don't you tell me
how I should be thinking?
Like a leader!
I am a leader!
Then where are your followers?
You can't force an agenda,
Mr. Alderson.
You have to inspire one.
Nice digs.
DiPIERRO: Remember,
I only let you in
because you said
you're not into girls.
No, I said I wasn't a lesbian,
end quote.
I didn't say
I wasn't into girls.
Very clever.
How about that nightcap?
Right, but only one.
I gotta work in the morning,
and you gotta get home
before curfew.
Screw curfew.
Hey, that rhymes.
An E Kit?
God, I can't believe
you bought into that shit.
You can never be too prepared.
Such a Girl Scout.
You think that's Girl Scout-y?
Mmm-hmm.
Check this out.
Alexa, give me the daily
Five/Nine.
Hello,
and welcome to your daily
Five/Nine report.
Officials advise to stay away
from the Upper East Side,
where armed theft
is at peak levels.
Impressive.
What else does that thing do?
Alexa, play John Prine.
Shuffling songs
by John Prine.
That's better.
Why you didn't go after
that blonde is beyond me.
She was mint.
Wasn't meant to be.
Whatevs. You didn't even try.
Jesus H., I think I'm drunk.
But it's...
Probably a good thing, 'cause I
have like legit trouble sleeping.
I take melatonin, but I gotta
down, like, six of them
to even get drowsy,
and then...
What was that?
It's cool.
No, it's...
No, it's not.
What am I doing?
This isn't professional.
Dude, you said it yourself.
I'm not a source anymore.
Believe it or not,
I'm actually a real person.
Darlene, seriously.
All right.
Fine. I'm sorry,
it's just...
I like you.
You're drunk.
Come on, at least give
me more credit than that.
Wait, hold on.
Um, one second.
You could've kept the gun on.
Don't overthink this.
We have to get moving.
We're not safe here.
I have to warn her. She has
to know what they heard.
I could just get
on the subway,
she'll find us like before.
She'll protect us.
Since the cyber bombings,
there's been a wave
of backlash against the FBI
from Americans of all backgrounds
and political views.
The one thing we heard over
and over from those...
was the sentiment that our law
enforcement agencies
can no longer be trusted.
You ready?
Yo, Dr. Wang.
How you doing?
And this is where
we part ways.
Peace, brother.
Your bag.
Where we going?
Shut the fuck up.
No questions.
I hear you have some
information on Stage 3.
I need my laptop.
It has my plans.
It's fine.
We can pull everything
we need from there.
Why don't you have a seat?
Your password?
The first time you and I met
to discuss the E Corp hack,
you said this was
a two-step plan.
So I'm sure you can imagine
my surprise
when out of the blue,
I now hear there is a third.
So, Mr. Alderson, why don't you
tell me what it is you want?
I asked for a meet
with Whiterose.
I'll relay any messages
to her.
I need to speak with her
directly.
You've had all the time you'll
ever get with Whiterose.
I thought she wanted
to kill E Corp.
Yes, I believe
that's what we did.
No, E Coin didn't exist
when we first created
this plan.
Now it's the only thing
keeping them afloat.
It's becoming the world
standard.
And E Cam's entire existence
relies upon it.
So what do you propose we do?
If you truly want to end them,
eliminating E Coin
is the only way.
Mr. Alderson,
is this everything
that you came
to discuss with me?
Anything else on your mind?
Are you in or out?
Goodbye, Mr. Alderson.
I got CDs,
everybody, come on!
They get you turnt!
Scan me .05 E Coin,
it's yours!
I got CDs! CDs! Yo,
this shit'll get you turnt!
All right, scan me .05 E Coin,
and it's yours!
Hey, these savage
tracks will give you life, yo.
No.
I will not take your CD
this time.
Ms. Moss?
Ms. Moss, I'm gonna need you
to come with us.
CDs! CDs!
This shit'll get you turnt!
Scan me .05 E Coin,
and it's yours!
We're ready.
So this is why you came here.
You're not talking your way
out of this.
Well, you were right.
Everything we did
was what they wanted.
Exactly.
Whiterose, Price, and who
the fuck knows who else?
I'm a prisoner
just like before.
Where does that leave me?
What am I supposed to do?
The CTO position is worthless.
You heard him.
We can use it.
You see how they operate?
In the shadows.
You just settle in,
smile, nod.
When the time is right...
we'll expose them.
Do you get it now?
E Corp, they might as well
be a front for them!
Whiterose, Price,
their friends,
they're the ones
we need to take down.
We just need a launching pad.
A place to begin, dig in.
Find that vulnerability.
The FBI.
The Dark Army has a man
on the inside.
I don't understand.
How do you not understand'?
You were trying to hack me.
An FBI agent.
And I already told you why.
Your bullshit's not gonna fly!
SANTIAGO; Enough!
You gonna fill me in?
Tell him.
Get fucked.
Every time you guys get intel,
one of my friends
ends up dead.
And Tyrell's bullshit release
was as pathetic
as a dry hand job.
Why should I trust you
or anyone else here?
The FBI is obviously
in bed with the Dark Army.
Where'd you hear that'?
Chew balls.
Just tell me.
Why is she here?
She was in my home, attempting to
steal my badge to get on Sentinel.
Full disclosure, Sir,
we had relations tonight.
I plan on self-reporting it
to the OPR.
I'm not keeping anything
from the Bureau.
Do you have any idea how fucking
big the crime you committed is?
You can forget about immunity
this time.
And why the hell were you trying
to get into Sentinel anyway?
You're in too deep
this time, Darlene.
You gotta talk.
There are files in Sentinel
that can help decrypt
all of E Corp's data.
That means bringing
everything back.
The solution to undoing
Five/Nine is in a machine
on the other side
of this floor, okay'?
They're in Romero's
collection.
Sit with me,
look over my shoulder,
I'll even walk through it
with your engineer, whatever.
You guys can personally
take the keys to E Corp
and be the heroes, okay?
You can fix everything.
Isn't that
what you want?
What you've been waiting for?
She's right! Wasn't this the
point of our entire strategy?
You need to understand
something...
This is the opportunity
we've been chasing!
You're missing the point.
We have nothing to lose.
If she's lying, we put her
in jail, but if she's not...
And what if our testimony
gets thrown out
because of your grossly
unprofessional behavior?
Sleeping with a CHS,
for Christ's sake.
She's not a CHS anymore.
And you know
I didn't break any rules.
So what's really
happening here?
Why not take her up
on her offer?
Get back to your desk
and write the 302
explaining your actions
minute by minute.
I'm assigning Agent Kaz
to Darlene.
That will continue to be
part of the debate...
What's the plan here? She talks
like she knows everything.
You sound stressed.
Of course, I'm fucking
stressed. I could be burnt.
Meanwhile, she claims
she can undo the hack.
And where is she now?
Locked in a goddamn
interview room.
Okay.
Is that all you've got?
"Okay"?
Jesus, will you just tell
me how do you want to proceed?
Not one box even packed?
I suppose there's some banal
excuse why a month
isn't enough time
for those lazy mules
to get my project shipped
to the Congo?
Border security.
Border security
across the Eastern seaboard
is restricted to levels
we've never seen before.
Hence, our extensive payroll.
We own mayors,
district attorneys,
governors, fucking presidents!
The country is
operating under martial law.
Our contacts are afraid.
You've always asked
that I be honest with you.
Speak.
This is your fault.
You blindly indulge all
of Elliot Alderson's whims.
And it has landed us here.
If you'd listened to me,
if you believed in my strategy
as much as you did his,
we could have avoided this.
We had the U.N. vote, these
attacks weren't necessary.
People like Phillip Price
do not respect mercy.
You only get their attention
with force and a lot of it.
That is the only currency
with these men.
I will go back to our partners
with a more persuasive
argument.
See? That's all
I needed to hear.
And...
What HOW?
I keep looking at this note,
wondering what Mr. Robot
did last night.
If the Dark Army
does own the FBI,
how did he find out?
Does it matter?
I don't need him.
Darlene will be checking
in soon about Sentinel,
and I have to enact Stage 3.
Mr. Alderson is claiming
there is a third stage.
He wants to target E Coin.
But I'm sure you knew
all along there is no Stage 3.
A third stage.
Odd.
That wasn't part of our
original plan, was it'?
NO.
So what do you make of that?
His sister is currently
being held at the FBI.
Claiming she can
decrypt E Cam's data.
I can't help but notice
their actions are incongruous.
He's lying to us.
I don't think their target
is E Corp anymore.
I think it's us.
When the Dark Army
operatives' malware
copies my file to their
command and control server...
Get yourself back to work.
It'll be queued up
for an operator
to review its contents.
Once opened, my exploit
will give me full access
to their management interface.
Why the dismay?
We expected something like
this out of him, did we not?
You never understood
my commitment to Mr. Alderson.
You say that I was wrong
to order the attack.
Maybe I'm wrong
about him as well.
So tell me,
what would you do
if you had your way?
And now,
1 own the Dark Army.
Do you remember when you said
Elliot will one day follow in
the footsteps of his father'?
I think it's time
he died for us, too.